<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:27:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Universities</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/universities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:25:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/universities/</guid>
      <description>A collaboration between professors from three universities set out to deliver a series of reports entitled, “The State of the Nation: A 50-State COVID-19 Survey”. Survey data was collected from over 20,000 individuals, who responded to questions about reopening, mitigation, health guidelines, and more, with the survey running every two weeks.
The Director of Polling at one of the universities involved with the project reached out to Crunch.io for an easy-to-use survey tool that could integrate data from multiple sources, including national and state databases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaming</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:54:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gaming/</guid>
      <description>A video game company uses survey data from players to showcase audience insights and sell sponsorships to its advertisers. They chose Crunch.io because of the increased efficiency and time saved analyzing data with the drag-and-drop platform. They work with Crunch.io to analyze tracker data across multiple countries.
In preparation for a partner event, the company analysts built and presented interactive dashboards customized for each of their partners with Crunch.io’s no-coding, drag-and-drop dashboard builder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gojek</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gojek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:47:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gojek/</guid>
      <description>Gojek is the leading on-demand multi-service app platform and digital payment technology group in Southeast Asia. The company uses a call center to connect consumers to courier delivery and ride-hailing services. As of mid-2019, Gojek was a “Decacorn” valued at over $10 billion dollars with over 3,000 employees.
Gojek values Crunch.io for its ability to handle large-scale surveys. The company analyzes multiple tracker waves of data across a dozen countries and several customer satisfaction surveys across their rewards programs and multiple product lines in Crunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/entertainment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:45:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/entertainment/</guid>
      <description>When COVID-19 hit, a leading live entertainment and ticketing company didn’t panic. Instead, they launched a large gen-pop survey of almost 10,000 people across 8 countries to research how the pandemic is affecting their customers’ willingness to go to live events in the future.
The insights team analyzed key results within 48 hours of field completion with Crunch’s easy-to-use online platform. They prepared, analyzed data, built dashboards and delivered PowerPoint slides all within a few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prodege</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/prodege/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 12:41:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/prodege/</guid>
      <description>Prodege is a leading provider of data and insights fueled by their global proprietary panel of 120 million members in over 125 countries. They leverage their innovative Prodege On-Demand platform (POD) to create and launch surveys for over 1,000 clients worldwide and chose to integrate Crunch.io within the POD platform so that their clients have access to data in exportable charts as well as online dashboards.
Prodege specializes in delivering fast, whether clients leverage Prodege’s managed services team of research experts or utilize their DIY version of POD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Council on Global Affairs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/chicago-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 11:22:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/chicago-council/</guid>
      <description>The Chicago Council on Global Affairs is an independent, nonpartisan organization that provides insight into global issues and policy.
The Chicago Council Survey team, part of the Lester Crown Center on US Foreign Policy, uses Crunch.io to analyze data from its annual survey on American public opinion and US foreign policy.
They have appended over 45 years of public opinion datasets into one dataset, previously only available in separate files, to enable simple and intuitive analysis of historical data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouGov</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/yougov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 18:39:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/yougov/</guid>
      <description>YouGov, whose current brand slogan is “the best panel - the best data - the best tools”, has one of the world’s largest research networks with a proprietary panel of over 17 million individuals in 50 markets. Researchers at YouGov use Crunch.io to perform analysis and deliver data and insights to clients via the Crunch.io web application, CrunchBoxes, and dashboards.
YouGov uses Crunch.io enterprise-wide for both custom research and Data Products, such as YouGov Profiles, which provides syndicated segmentation and product data for agencies and brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated dataset menu and dataset properties</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/updated-dataset-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:27:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/updated-dataset-properties/</guid>
      <description>Now dataset editors can access most dataset actions directly from the dataset menu. Additionally, we’ve redesigned our dataset properties page.
New dataset menu
When you click the dataset name from within a dataset, you may notice some changes to the dropdown menu:
Many of the actions that used to be accessed through Dataset properties can now be performed directly from this menu. Specifically Export dataset, Append, Join, Organize variables, Exclude cases, and (under Advanced), Create draft and View dataset history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix categories to the bottom of lists when sorting</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/fix-categories-when-sorting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:41:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/fix-categories-when-sorting/</guid>
      <description>We understand that when creating analyses for export or dashboards, certain answer categories carry different significance. &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;, “Other” and &amp;ldquo;None of these&amp;rdquo; are three such examples that often require special handling. With Crunch&amp;rsquo;s latest feature, you can now effortlessly fix these categories, or any others of your choosing, to the end of your lists when sorting, ensuring that they are sensibly placed at the end and not merged in amongst your brand lists, attitude statements, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigate, locate, and organize datasets more easily</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/project-folder-sidebar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 09:43:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/project-folder-sidebar/</guid>
      <description>We’re excited to share the newest update to dataset folder navigation. We’ve added a tree view of the folders shared with you to the left side of the “all datasets” page, so you can browse and move more easily between subfolders.
Editors and administrators can use the sidebar to organize folders and subfolders by dragging and dropping. Viewers can see the organization of any folder trees shared with them and navigate between different folders and subfolders they have access to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easily create and share subsets of your datasets with different user groups</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-views/</guid>
      <description>Dataset Views: Quickly Create, Deliver, and Share Data Subsets
It’s increasingly common to collect data for multiple clients or multiple groups of stakeholders in one single survey. Whether for an Omnibus product, a syndicated data product or simply different regional groupings, it can be challenging to meet the different data needs of these client and stakeholder groups with a single dataset. To meet this need, Crunch has developed Dataset Views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give a great welcome to your customers by branding and customizing the appearance of folders</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/folder-homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 15:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/folder-homepage/</guid>
      <description>Crunch’s folders give you the power to organize your datasets and control access. Now folders can also be a great landing page for new and existing data consumers.
Folder Homepages can contain images, formatted text, embedded videos and links to other resources to provide Crunch customization, as well as to aide in navigation to other resources such as terms and conditions. You can tailor the experience for your teammates and clients when they arrive into Crunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subtotals and calculated differences can now be shown on graphs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/graphing-subtotals-and-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 21:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/graphing-subtotals-and-differences/</guid>
      <description>Subtotals have been a feature of Crunch for years, and calculated differences were added to the feature set in May 2021. They&amp;rsquo;ve been popular features in tables and thanks to this latest release, they&amp;rsquo;re now available in graphs too. Both subtotals and differences can now be displayed in graphs in Tables &amp;amp; Graphs mode, as well as on dashboards and in PPTX exports, giving you the flexibility to display, save and report these summary statistics just like any other variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export Crunch survey results in a BI-ready format</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-tabulated-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 15:18:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-tabulated-data/</guid>
      <description>Crunch gives you the best of all worlds — you analyze all your survey data in Crunch, and now you can export those results into your other reporting tools (such as Tableau, Google Data Studio, PowerBI) so that you can see your survey results alongside your other business metrics.
Your tables (tab books) can now be exported in a specialized output format. This format contains a row for each cell of the table you see in the Crunch app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a grouping (array) of numeric variables for easy comparison</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/numeric-arrays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 14:05:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/numeric-arrays/</guid>
      <description>Numeric Arrays enable you to work efficiently with groups of numeric variables that are related. For example, you might have asked your respondents for the number of times they have engaged with each of a list of activities, or asked for how many times they&amp;rsquo;ve purchased each of a list of products, or asked for a numeric rating for how much they agree with a list of statements. In each case, the data collected consist of a set of numeric values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add subtotals to multiple response variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals-mr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 12:30:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals-mr/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors have been able to add subtotals (a.k.a. “nets”) to categorical and categorical array variables for a long time, but this hasn’t been the case for multiple response variables. There are many applications for subtotals on multiple response variables — a common one is a group of products or sub-brands within a brand, or a grouping of statements into themes. Previously, users had to define new variables with often complex logic to describe each combination, and then hide the input variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch&#39;s new visualizations for time-series analyses and trackers are now extended to Date/Time variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/date-time-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 13:39:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/date-time-variables/</guid>
      <description>Back in April this year, we announced that a great new visualization was available for time series analyses that used the new &amp;ldquo;Categorical Date&amp;rdquo; variable type. Existing time plots that used the older Date/Time variable type were unaffected and continued to use the previous line graph component. Since then, we&amp;rsquo;ve worked to extend the new line graph functionality to those original Date/Time variables so that everyone can benefit from their better design and functionality, and we can now announce that all time plots will be using the new visualization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort your graph categories automatically</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sort-by-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 11:27:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sort-by-value/</guid>
      <description>You’ve been able to sort categories in tables in Crunch for a long time, but previously when you switched to a graph, that sorting was lost and the graph would show the categories in their original variable order. Now, the sorting you apply in a table will be carried through into a graph when you switch visualization type, as well as being made part of the analysis definition when you save a graph to the deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show calculated differences between categories</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotal-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 13:27:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotal-differences/</guid>
      <description>You’ve been able to create subtotals in Crunch for a long time, and they’re great for quickly seeing what proportion of respondents hold similar views, such as any level of agreement with a statement or any level of liking of a brand etc. But sometimes you also need to take into account the strength of opposing views — those who disagree or those who dislike, and for that you want to sum those who agree and take away the sum of those who disagree, leaving you with an overall measure you can use for simple comparisons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great new visualizations for time-series analyses and trackers</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-time-plots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 08:20:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-time-plots/</guid>
      <description>Line graphs are great at showing how values are changing over time and therefore ideal for tracking studies. Crunch&amp;rsquo;s line graphs have been completely redesigned to offer some great new features as well as improved usability and flexibility.
Category selection
Line graphs become really hard to read when there are lots of lines shown simultaneously, so Crunch now defaults to showing just the top 5, but you can pick whichever combination of lines (including showing more or fewer than 5) from the new &amp;ldquo;Select categories&amp;rdquo; interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch Automation: A blueprint for building a solid home for your data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/blog/automation/crunch-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 11:44:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/blog/automation/crunch-automation/</guid>
      <description>Crunch Automation serves as a declarative history of transformations that have been done to a dataset. This is important to understand, because it informs you how you go about writing, running, editing and replicating datasets.
With SPSS syntax, it
directly manipulates an SPSS datafile (eg: .sav file) is not designed with survey analysis in mind doesn’t set up derivations like Crunch does (it hard-codes anything you do as a new variable) doesn’t stay with the datafile (you keep your syntax separate from the datafile), and, importantly, alters your variables by overwriting the already-hard-coded variables with more syntax (which you can do endlessly) Crunch Automation is the opposite in these respects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplified options for Dataset Sharing</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-sharing/</guid>
      <description>The sharing options for a dataset have been simplified and consolidated. Previously, both Share and Members links were visible to Dataset Editors. To simplify, Dataset Editors can only now see the Members link. The Share link option for Dataset Editors has been removed.
For Dataset Viewers, the sharing option with Share link has not changed.
Below we have outlined how you can share a dataset for different permission levels: Editors and Viewers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the margin of error and other helpful statistics in tables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</guid>
      <description>By using the new options panel revealed by clicking the three-dots icon in the display controller, users can choose which of these figures to display in the tooltip for table cells. The default statistics shown are the margin of error and unweighted base. Your chosen cell details are persisted as a user preference. For margin of error, you can also specify the number of decimal places you want to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greater flexibility to customize exports of tables from decks and dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-export-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:00:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-export-settings/</guid>
      <description>Back in September, we added a variety of advanced calculations to include in tab books (exported multitables) and other options to customize the exported tables. We&amp;rsquo;ve now added these same customization options to tables saved to (and exported from) the deck.
This can be helpful if you need to:
Show more than one measure (percentages, counts, indices, Z-scores, population estimates) at once, or
Have additional elements or measures included in your exports, such as pairwise comparison letters (ABCD), standard deviations, standard errors, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perform trend analysis on wave data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In time series analysis, we want to be able to identify trends. As we collect data, random fluctuations can obfuscate a trend. Smoothing is an analytic process whereby we ‘iron out’ differences between time periods by taking the average of previous periods. This is also known as a moving average. You can now apply smoothing to your analyses with just a few clicks. In the smoothing tab accessed by clicking ⋮ select ‘One-sided moving average’ and choose the number of periods to ‘look back’ at each point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greater flexibility to customize tab books</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 16:12:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</guid>
      <description>You can now choose a variety of advanced calculations to include in tab books (exported multitables) and other options to customize the exported tables. Table cells can now contain estimates of standard deviation and standard error, and column summaries can include the median of numeric values as well as the standard deviation for the column and standard error of the mean. Pairwise column significance tests can be conducted at the standard 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export dashboards or the tabs you want, with the new selective tab exports feature</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 09:39:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</guid>
      <description>Exporting from dashboards just got more flexible. Instead of always having to export the whole dashboard, users are now able to choose between exporting the whole dashboard (still the default), exporting the currently viewed tab, or choosing a custom selection of one or more tabs to export.
The new, simplified “Export…” option opens the new Export panel which gives the choice of PowerPoint or Excel formats, but for dashboards with tabs, it also now contains a “Tabs” control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combine categories in dashboard filter variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</guid>
      <description>The Groups on dashboards can now optionally allow multiple category selections to effectively combine categories in the filter. Dashboard editors can set an option on the configuration screen for dashboard “Groups” that allows users to make multiple selections within each variable. For example, if you choose an age categories variable as a group and turn on this new option, the dashboard users will be able to select both “18–24” and “25–34” simultaneously, thereby creating a filter that includes anyone aged 18–34.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customize your tables for export or dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 09:26:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve already been able to customize saved graphs, but now you can make those same edits to the rows and columns of saved tables, either for export or for display in dashboards. More specifically, you can now&amp;hellip;
Hide any rows and/or columns of a table, including calculated rows/columns such as subtotals, leaving only those you want your export/dashboard consumers to see. Simply uncheck the box next to the row/column to hide it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easily create and recombine categorical arrays and multiple response variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-multiple-response-cat-array-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:34:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-multiple-response-cat-array-builder/</guid>
      <description>Array variables allow you to analyze together a set of variables that share a common structure and theme. For example, surveys often ask respondents to use a common scale to rate or respond to different prompts, sometimes in a grid, all sharing a common set of response categories. When analyzing the data, a categorical array variable lets users see all the items together. This structure allows users to easily compare lists of brands against a common set of attributes, or compare a set of statements against a common agreement scale — something that is much harder to do with distinct categorical variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use custom color palettes for your saved analyses</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 12:14:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been possible for some time to set custom colors for saved analyses in Crunch, but it&amp;rsquo;s been necessary to do this on a one-by-one basis which can be laborious and open to inconsistency. We now offer the ability to create custom color palettes, defined at the organization level, at folder levels, or both, which apply your chosen colors to newly created analyses as well as offering alternatives (e.g. for scales) that can be applied easily, as needed for particular analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect your PowerPoint decks with many new edit controls</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:11:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</guid>
      <description>When you create an analysis, you may need to edit it further for a PowerPoint export: for example, perhaps you want to hide &amp;lsquo;Not sure&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Prefer not to answer&amp;rsquo; categories, rename long labels, re-order the categories, give the whole analysis a descriptive title, or even simply change the coloring. You can now make these adjustments and more, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find all of those changes reflected in your PowerPoint and Excel exports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show value labels on graphs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</guid>
      <description>Users can now decide whether to show value labels for graphs and charts, both in Tables &amp;amp; Graphs mode and on dashboards. Value labels are these small numbers on graphs that show you the value represented by that bar/column/segment&amp;hellip;
With the new feature turned on, these value labels will be displayed on all graphs you create. With the feature turned off (the default), the user needs to hover over a chart element to see a tool-tip with this value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding KPI tiles to dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-kpi-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:03:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-kpi-tile/</guid>
      <description>Dashboards can now contain KPI analyses that take a single value from a table and present it in a tile. Great for when there&amp;rsquo;s a key metric you want to highlight or track.
Dataset editors can now add KPI analyses like these to dashboards. This allows you to show a key company metric – e.g. Brand Awareness – as a prominent value that grabs attention.
To create one, simply save an analysis of any kind – table, chart or variable card – that contains the value you want to show as a KPI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the interaction of two variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</guid>
      <description>To look in detail at your data, you sometimes need to create a variable that is the interaction of other categorical variables. You want to know not just how results differ between age groups or education level, but by age × education. The Crunch application lets you do this in just a few clicks by selecting the variables to interact — give the result a name (or accept the default of ‘x by y’) and you’re set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard tabs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</guid>
      <description>Dashboard tiles can now be placed across multiple tabs, making it easier to navigate large dashboards. As an editor, you are now able to:
Create new tabs (as many as you&amp;rsquo;d like)
Move tiles from one tab to another
Give tabs meaningful names to aid navigation
Delete tabs, choosing whether to delete any tiles or move them to another tab
See our support documentation to get started.
We&amp;rsquo;d love your feedback at support@crunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch&#39;s updated Member panels make it easy to see who has access to a dataset or folder</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-permissions-september-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 15:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-permissions-september-2019/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve made it much easier to view and change which of your users have access to your datasets and folders. If you are an editor on a dataset or folder, click the dataset or folder name in the header and select Members to open the permissions panel:
When viewing dataset members, this panel will show all users who have access to this dataset and what type of access they have, regardless of how that access was granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding rich-text tiles to dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 13:07:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can now add rich-text tiles to a dashboard. This can be used for dashboard analysis, terms and conditions, privacy notices, fieldwork dates and anything else the editor may wish to display. As an editor you are now able to:
Compose text content to display as tiles using a WYSIWYG editor - no coding skills required.
See a real-time preview of how your tile is going to look as you type and make formatting changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtering dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 10:16:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can add one or more variables to be used as filters across an entire dashboard with a simple drag-and-drop interface. This allows all dashboard viewers to get more out of your dashboards by customizing their view of the data. For example:
Add demographic variables such as gender, age, education level, region, and ethnicity to allow your viewers to drill down on the customer populations that interest them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click to set the comparison column for hypothesis tests</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/click-to-compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/click-to-compare/</guid>
      <description>Tables in the application now let you set a column as the basis of comparison, shading the table to show which other columns are higher or lower than the reference column, and to what level of statistical significance. The test is a two-tailed t test comparing each column proportion in turn to the proportion in the reference column. In a multitable, the test is conducted between categories within each column variable, and not across column variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizable dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 09:56:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</guid>
      <description>What are Crunch dashboards? A dashboard is a special view of your data that has been prepared with pre-made analyses — tables and graphs — designed to highlight key points for instant insight. Dashboards are great for conveying key information, drawn from your data, for users who don’t have the time (or the inclination) to do their own analysis. Crunch dashboards allow you to combine your important findings into a single display, perfect for sharing with colleagues and other end users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New hypothesis testing features in Crunch</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-hypothesis-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-hypothesis-tests/</guid>
      <description>Crunch tab book exports now include a new hypothesis testing option that computes all possible comparisons between columns of a two-way table. When users select the &amp;ldquo;Column t-test&amp;rdquo; option in the “Export tab book… &amp;gt; Customize” panel, columns in output will be lettered and differences that are significant at the .05 significance level are indicated by letters underneath the cell with the higher percentage. See here for details.
An example of the exported result is shown below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Multitable Export</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-this-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-this-table/</guid>
      <description>Export all on a single page Multitables are a great way to quickly find key relationships in your data. When exporting multitables, you now have three choices, allowing you to create just the right export for your needs.
Export this table – instantly grab an XLSX file of just what you see on screen, using whatever display settings you have currently selected. Export this table (saved settings) – instantly grab an XLSX file of the table that you see on screen but with whatever settings you’ve chosen in the Export tab book &amp;gt; Customize panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Organization of Datasets</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</guid>
      <description>Dataset folders allow you to organize your data hierarchically, similar to a file system as you might see in Windows Explorer or MacOS Finder. Folders make finding, organizing, and sharing data more intuitive.
Folders can be used to organize large collections of datasets into more manageable units. If your organization imports data from many sources or has a large archive of previously imported data, you can organize them by source, time of import/survey, subject, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Manager, Database Systems</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/software-project-manager-crunchdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 04:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/software-project-manager-crunchdb/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP Software Engineering
Work location: North America, 100% remote
Employment type: Full-time employee, direct hire
Direct reports: 10 to 12 software engineers
We are hiring an Engineering Manager to help expand our platform and operations excellence. The successful candidate will have been a software engineer and has grown into a project manager and team manager role. We invite you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators, helping make our platform faster, more secure, and reliable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights Tech Showcase: Brand Tracking</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/brand-tracking-demo-2022</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 11:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/brand-tracking-demo-2022</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insight Platforms Demo Days</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/demo-days-2022</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 12:20:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/demo-days-2022</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Success Manager</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/customer-success-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:21:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/customer-success-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Customer Success
Work Location: Remote, United States, preferably EST or CST time zones
Are you a technically-oriented, quantitative market researcher looking for a change in direction? You should consider putting your technical skills to work in software, specifically, analytic software for market research.
Crunch.io is a rapidly growing, market-defining company in the analytics SaaS marketplace. We’re a company on the rise. We’ve built a revolutionary platform that transforms our customers’ ability to drive insight from market research and survey data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Development Representative</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/sales-development-representative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:21:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/sales-development-representative/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Sales Director
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada, Seattle preferred
What you&amp;rsquo;ll do
The Sales Development Representative (SDR) will have responsibility for qualifying leads that build pipelines for the sales organization as well as closing non-enterprise deals. The SDR will follow up on web inquiries, pre‐qualify leads, close opportunities, and develop larger leads to the point of handoff to outside sales. In addition to inbound inquiries, the SDR will perform prospecting, marketing event outreach, and perform general sales development functions to build a pipeline within targeted accounts designated by management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Manager</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/product-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:29:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/product-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Product Development
Work location: Remote, United States
Contract type: Permanent | Full-time
People manager: No
Crunch.io is seeking a Product Manager, to help us build the tools for the next generation of analytics tools for survey data. You will align with our workflows team, based in US Mountain Time, providing them with both big picture product vision and day-to-day delivery support. You will collaborate internally and externally to develop a vision for how users can work together to share and move data and insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Go Online: Self-Service Data Analysis for Insights Teams</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/tmre-brands-webinar-2021-lp</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:51:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/tmre-brands-webinar-2021-lp</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IIEX Forward Demo: Fast Track Your Survey Data Analysis with an All-in-One Platform</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/iiex-forward-demo-2021</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 16:00:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/iiex-forward-demo-2021</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Support Analyst</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/customer-support-analyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 14:41:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/customer-support-analyst/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Manager of Customer Service
Work location: Remote
Do you work with market research data? Looking for a change of direction away from traditional market research data processing and analysis? Here is an opportunity to join the supplier side, in software.
We have a growing product and user base and need an organized, detail-oriented person to join our customer support team for our online data analysis and reporting app: Crunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey Data Analysis Trends: Your Data in One Place or All Over the Place?</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/quirks-virtual-crunch-session-2021</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 16:32:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/quirks-virtual-crunch-session-2021</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights Tech Showcase Demo</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/insights-analytics-showcase-2021</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 15:31:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/insights-analytics-showcase-2021</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Static Reporting &amp; PowerPoint</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/quirks-virtual-fall-crunch-lp</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 11:07:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/quirks-virtual-fall-crunch-lp</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Normal in Market Research: Delivering Tracking Survey Insights in 24 Hours</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/quirks-virtual-crunch-lp</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 14:21:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/quirks-virtual-crunch-lp</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization Specialist</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/data-visualization-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 11:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/data-visualization-specialist/</guid>
      <description>We are looking for a world-class Data Visualization Specialist to join our remote-first and globally distributed team at Crunch.io—the platform for collaborative data analysis. In this role, you will be working with a team of data scientists, industry experts, market research organizations, designers, and engineers; creating cutting-edge data visualizations for companies ranging from small-to-medium sized businesses to Fortune 500 organizations. This remote position reports to our VP of Product and will work closely with our Senior Director of Analytics and Product, Design, and Engineering teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboards 101: Design Tips for Market Researchers</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/dashboards-tips-and-tricks-lp</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 17:28:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/dashboards-tips-and-tricks-lp</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch.io Overview</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/343376948</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 10:50:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/343376948</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Conquer Survey Trackers</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/conquering-survey-trackers-lp</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 17:10:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/conquering-survey-trackers-lp</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch.io Dashboards Overview</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/374781211</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 17:05:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/374781211</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 17:05:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/</guid>
      <description>Interested in learning more about Crunch?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build an Interactive Dashboard for Survey Data in 5 Minutes</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/dashboards-webinar-recording-lp</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 17:05:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/dashboards-webinar-recording-lp</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a CrunchBox</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/367372910/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 17:00:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/367372910/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use a CrunchBox</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/367372890/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 16:59:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/367372890/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Software Delivery Manager
Work location: Anywhere, 100% remote
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring a Python Developer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features and build the future for how we deploy our products faster and safer while increasing the availability and reliability of our systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Database Architect</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/senior-db-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/senior-db-programmer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Software Delivery Manager
Work location: Anywhere, 100% remote
Employment type: Full-time employee, direct hire
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring a Senior Database Architect to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features and build the future for how we deploy our products faster and safer while increasing the availability and reliability of our systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Support</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/help.crunch.io/hc/en-us</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 17:15:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/help.crunch.io/hc/en-us</guid>
      <description>Looking for help with Crunch?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced React Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/react-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:45:00 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/react-developer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Software Delivery Manager
Work location: Anywhere, 100% remote
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring an Advanced React Developer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features, explore different ways of problem solving, and discover, explain, and defend your choices in implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importing and Cleaning Data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/knowledge-base/importing-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 15:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/knowledge-base/importing-data/</guid>
      <description>Importing data Importing data is so much fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/knowledge-base/sharing-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 15:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/knowledge-base/sharing-data/</guid>
      <description>Sharing Data Sharing data is really fun</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Executive</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United Kingdom
The Account Executive (AE) will be responsible for driving sales of Crunch products within an assigned geographical region and market segment. The AE will represent Crunch and manage all aspects of the sales process including: lead management, qualification, evaluation, close and account care and will play an integral role in the success of the overall sales team. This is a quota‐carrying sales position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/knowledge-base/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/knowledge-base/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada
The Account Executive will be responsible for driving sales of Crunch products within an assigned geographical region and market segment. The AE will represent Crunch and manage all aspects of the sales process including: lead management, qualification, evaluation, close and account care and will play an integral role in the success of the overall sales team. This is a quota‐carrying sales position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insight Platforms Demo Days</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/demo-days-2022</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/demo-days-2022</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights Tech Showcase Brand Tracking</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/brand-tracking-demo-sep-2022</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/brand-tracking-demo-sep-2022</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TMRE</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/tmre-2022</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/info.crunch.io/tmre-2022</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.17</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-12-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following: Materialization of formulas works properly now when a dataset exclusion filter is applied. Users were sometimes not able to export a multitable that contains a formula weight, which has now been fixed. Passing a variable through a function signature was triggering a type conversion when using the CSV importer, which has been fixed. A bug occurred that prevented users from editing personal variables, which has also been fixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.16</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-11-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-11-21/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following in Confirmit integrations: A bug that occurred within surveys that define predefined lists within predefined lists. Confirmit titles with empty strings (&amp;quot;&amp;quot;) are now given a default title (&amp;quot;No Title”). A category mapping is now used to fix column aliases when a grid variable is a categorical array. Numeric arrays are now handled properly when there is missing data due to broken labeling. Fixed the size limit for response data on Decipher integrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.15</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-10-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-10-24/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added SAML SSO as an option for user authentication in Crunch. SAML is a secure, industry standard way for organizations to centrally manage users across applications. See the help article for more information. Fixed the ability to edit the definition of logical variables (those created in the filter builder) when using the web app. Fixed table exports so that pairwise column tests between multiple-response columns (when some columns are hidden) now work properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.14</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-09-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-09-27/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred in Crunchboxes, where only unweighted values displayed instead of their weighted ones. They now display weighted values. Completed a change to ensure that Excel cells that contain text cannot be incorrectly evaluated by Excel as formulas. Completed all of the updates to ensure that deck dashboards respected a mix of weighted and unweighted tiles correctly. Fixed a bug that affected users that have permissions to datasets in more than a single account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.13</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-09-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred when CrunchBoxes did not display weighted values when applicable. Crunch integrations Made numerous Confirmit-integration fixes, including: Improved how categories are handled. Fixed HTML image-tag spacing issues. Fixed how subvariables and variables are imported, as well as ensuring that multiple/duplicate subvariable aliases are handled correctly. Corrected category IDs so that they are instead treated as integers (and not strings). Made additional looping and parsing fixes to further optimize Confirmit integrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The survey analysis tool you need</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/market-researchers/the-survey-analysis-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 17:17:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/market-researchers/the-survey-analysis-tool/</guid>
      <description> Weighting Stats testing Advanced filters (nesting variables) Custom interactions Multiway tables or 3D tables with 3 variables Time series charts Grids &amp;amp; scorecards </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>testimonial</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/market-researchers/testimonial-custumer-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 17:17:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/market-researchers/testimonial-custumer-research/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Crunch.io has been very successful for our clients. In the past, all clients’ queries channeled through us.
Now, clients are using Crunch.io by themselves to answer their own questions. They are less reliant on us for inquiries, freeing up my team’s time.”
DIRECTOR, CONSUMER RESEARCH, Nielsen IQ</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.12</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-08-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-08-08/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following issues: Slides were sometimes not appearing properly within a deck. Some columns within a multitable were no longer visible after decreasing the browser page magnification. Double-clicking on a tile in dashboard view did not switch to ‘tables &amp;amp; graphs’ view. Changes made to the sorting order of a univariate analysis in the Edit &amp;gt; Categories panel were not able to be saved. Crunch integrations Made the following Confirmit-integration fixes: Responses now load properly when the capitalization doesn&amp;rsquo;t match the metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work quicker and more efficiently</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/market-researchers/work-quicker-and-moreefficiently/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 17:17:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/market-researchers/work-quicker-and-moreefficiently/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.11</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-07-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-07-18/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Made the following improvements to tab book exports: Fixed the error messaging that appears when something fails during the export of a tab book. The values list within an exported tab book is now returned in the specified order for variables and subvariables. A bug previously prevented the order to output properly, which has been fixed. Improved Confirmit integrations by enabling surveys that have image-based fields. Enabled numeric means so that they can be: Rendered as a bar graph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Resources</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/free-resource/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:37:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/free-resource/</guid>
      <description>12 tips and tricks to build visually compelling, easily-digestible survey data dashboard that you can mae without an in-house designer or developer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.10</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-06-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-06-27/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following issues: Sharing of decks, filters, and multitables now works for subfolders so there is no longer a need to share the subfolder with a team as well. When exporting a tab book, it would sometimes fail when using certain setting combinations. The ‘edit tile footer’ field would sometimes display an inconsistent response when typing values into it. Made performance improvements to Confirmit integrations. Crunch Automation Fixed the following issues: The CREATE TEXT CONCATENATE command now works with categorical and text variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.09</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-05-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-05-30/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following in Confirmit integrations: Errors occurred when non-numeric category IDs are used. Surveys were not being displayed because they exist on subsequent pages. Fixed the following in the web ap: The numeric scale for a CrunchBox could mismatch the selected measure. Changes to the ‘Min’ and ‘Max’ value axis settings for a graph were not persisting. Enabled Dataset Views (in early access). See the announcement and documentation for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.08</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-05-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-05-02/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following issues: Certain messages were not sent to clients who have requested notification, specifically for dataset sharing. Time plots using categorical dates with the date format YYYY-Www were not rendering properly. Time plots would sometimes not save properly to the deck. Scorecard creation would sometimes not work. Vertical scrolling was not working properly for folders that have homepages defined for them. Updated the Decipher variable format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.07</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-04-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-04-11/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Folder Homepages is now available in wide release. Made the following PowerPoint export improvements: Removed the “All” title from exports of univariate bar graphs. Exports for a tabbed graph analysis now reflect the tab&amp;rsquo;s name corresponding to the data on the slide. Fixed the following issues: The search query was not working properly when a query contained an ampersand (&amp;amp;) character. Graph categories were rendered with incorrect colors if certain categories were suppressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.06</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-03-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-03-28/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following issues: Rollup changes did not reflect on tables and graphs. Filter footnotes did not display properly in graphs. PowerPoint exports of graphs failed if one or more categories were suppressed. The rendering of discrete values for a numeric variable did not appear in ‘tables &amp;amp; graphs’ view. Image links in exported markdown files did not work. Help desk and website improvements Created the Crunch naming rules article, which provides the latest guidance on how to name variables and folders to ensure that your data appears properly within the Crunch UI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.05</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-03-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-03-14/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed the following issues: Multitable column header titles and descriptions could sometimes overlap. An analysis with a multiple response variable in the column position and means in the cell positions may show dashes instead of actual means. Exporting a tabbook would sometimes fail to report that an error occurred during the processing of a request. Timeplots would sometimes not save to a deck successfully. Improved numeric array analyses so that blank columns are now suppressed if the setting to show empty rows/columns is not checked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.04</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-02-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-02-28/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that prevented all categories in the column position to be viewed when scrolling horizontally. Fixed an issue in which scorecard column headers would sometimes render on top of each other. Adjusted the limit on the number of tabs in a tab book (multitable) export to 500. Improved the user experience when viewing a time plot so that the top five categories displayed by default are now updated accordingly if the measure is changed in the display controller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.03</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-02-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-02-14/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Made performance improvements for rendering tables in dashboard tiles. Fixed an issue that occurred when double-clicking on a tile in dashboard view would sometimes not load the corresponding analysis in ‘tables &amp;amp; graphs’ view. Fixed an issue in which scorecard column headers could sometimes render overlapped (early access only). Added the ability to show subtotals and calculated differences on graphs, which is now in wide access. See the announcement for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.02</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-02-01/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an error that occurred in SurveyMonkey integrations when a “total” is not present in passed arguments. Added the ability to export datasets in the Parquet file format, which allows users to select categorical IDs to generate a more efficient Parquet file (the default export for categorical columns is column names). Added the ability to notify users when an invalid filter is applied as well as allow users to fix them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2022.01</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-01-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2022-01-10/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an error that disabled the ability for Confirmit-integrated datasets to be updated. API endpoints and API reference Added a new field to the View Filter Details endpoint (definition), which is a CrunchCL expression that represents the filter at the time it was created or last modified. SDKs (rCrunch, pyCrunch, and sCrunch) Made further updates and improvements to the latest versions of pyCrunch (v0.5.1) and sCrunch (v0.10.0). Crunch Automation Added a new optional argument (INCLUDE MISSING) to the CREATE MULTIPLE SELECTION command, which allows you to mark all-missing rows as valid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.42</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-12-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-12-20/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred with Confirmit integrations that sometimes caused imports to fail for some datasets with certain configurations of numeric variables. Added the ability to omit categories from PowerPoint graph exports in situations where a base size is less than the configured minimum one, when the dataset has been configured for the ‘Suppress’ setting. SDKs (rCrunch, pyCrunch, and sCrunch) Released new versions of [pyCrunch](https://pypi.org/project/pycrunch/) (v0.5.1) and [sCrunch](https://pypi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.41</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-12-06/</guid>
      <description>API endpoints and API reference Added a new query parameter (aliases) to the List variable definitions API endpoint, which provides faster access to the variable definitions, especially if the dataset includes a large number of variables. Crunch Automation Added the ability to specify a NUMERIC VALUE to the following commands: CREATE CATEGORICAL CASE command CREATE CATEGORICAL RECODE command CREATE ARRAY CASE command REPLACE ARRAY CASE command REPLACE CATEGORICAL CASE command REPLACE CATEGORICAL RECODE command CREATE CATEGORICAL CUT command Added the ability to modify only a subset of an array&amp;rsquo;s subvariables by using the SUBVARIABLES option in the CHANGE LABELS command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.40</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-11-15/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred when sorting on the Unweighted &amp;lsquo;N&amp;rsquo; column of an analysis and then saving it to the deck sometimes did not work properly. API endpoints and API reference Enhanced the documentation for creating, updating, and deleting API keys. SDKs (rCrunch, pyCrunch, and sCrunch) Added the following enhancements to the Crunch package for R: make and edit markdown slides, including images. create slides with more than one filter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find insights faster</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/origanize/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:17:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/origanize/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find insights right away</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/find-insigths-right-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:17:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/find-insigths-right-away/</guid>
      <description>Crunch.io’s automated import process preps your data for analysis so you can start analyzing as soon as your survey is out of field, or even sooner.
Data cleaning Clear naming &amp;amp; labels Questions organized into logical folders New tracker waves appends </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is as easy as it </title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/self-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:17:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/self-service/</guid>
      <description>Stop scavenging for SPSS files and spreadsheets. Easily collaborate with your whole team. Instantly search across all your projects&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>webinar</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 17:17:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/for-insights-teams/webinar/</guid>
      <description>Instantly analyze all your respondent-level data from multiple vendors online, in one place, available 24/7. Automate the creation of deliverables, including fully-editable PowerPoints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.39</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-11-01/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred when anchoring a subtotal from the last category instead of the bottom position, which sometimes resulted in incorrect behavior in the web application. Fixed an issue in Confirmit integrations that lead to some missing loop variables. Fixed an issue that occurred when &amp;lsquo;Set comparison&amp;rsquo; was selected for one variable in a multitable definition that includes multiple variables: it instead shaded a column across all of the variables but only performed the &amp;lsquo;Set comparison&amp;rsquo; for the first variable even if it was not the one targeted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.38</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-10-18/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred when sorting a bivariate table where the column variable had an intermediate category with N=0 followed by at least one category with N&amp;gt;0. Added a visual footnote to support the following features in the Crunch UI: within the export output — the footnote reflects when standard errors of test statistics have been adjusted for overlap between columns of a multiple response variable. within in tables &amp;amp; graphs and multitable views — the footnote reflects when standard errors of test statistics have been adjusted for overlap between columns of a multiple response variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.37</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-10-04/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Made the following fixes: KPIs are now correctly set to a table cell when viewing a multiple response analysis. Category hiding and color assignment are now correctly reflected in a dashboard tile. Category labels that have been renamed using &amp;lsquo;Edit tile&amp;rsquo; now show the correct label (vs. the original label) when sorting in a dashboard tile. A properly formatted table now appears when switching between &amp;lsquo;Multitable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; graphs&amp;rsquo; views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.36</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-27/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Made the following color assignment corrections: in deck analyses that include a multiple response variable with subtotals. in a categorical variable that has subtotals/differences defined for it. Added an &amp;lsquo;Insufficient Data&amp;rsquo; message on a tile, which appears when dashboard tiles have no results due to group filtering. Added the ability to drag tiles to a new location on the current dashboard tab by using only one drag-and-drop action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.35</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-20/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred when a tab on a dashboard tile was not allowing the user to change the selection. Improved the behavior in the &amp;lsquo;Dashboards Group&amp;rsquo; panel in situations when one or more of the filter variables have been deleted from the dataset. Fixed an issue that occurred when selecting a category in the &amp;lsquo;Dashboard Group&amp;rsquo; panel that sometimes did not reflect in the rendering of the dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.34</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-13/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that occurred when a filter is created by dragging a variable from &amp;ldquo;My variables&amp;rdquo; to the filter zone so that it now works correctly. Fixed an issue that occurred when an unexpected format for the filter definition sometimes causes a dashboard tile to not load properly. API endpoints and API reference Updated the folder endpoint to obtain the variable organization script so that it now returns a shoji:view as default, but will return a plain text response if requested with the Accept HTTP header text/plain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.33</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-06/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Updated the Crunch UI so that deck slides and dashboard tiles are correctly weighted with the updated variable when a weight variable is deleted and re-created with the same alias. Improved Qualtrics integrations, which now support embedded data. Updated how &amp;lsquo;Unweighted N / All&amp;rsquo; column values appear so that they now correctly display in multitable view when the row variable is a categorical array. Added the ability to allow a dataset editor to reorder the slides of a deck that are owned by another user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.32</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-30/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Updated data exports so that hidden multiple response subtotals are no longer included. Improved the &amp;lsquo;Select Categories&amp;rsquo; panel for a time plot so that it now displays multiple response subtotals in the correct order. Help desk and website improvements Created a new article that describes how to use a CSV + JSON metadata document to automate the setup of a dataset. Organized the Sharing Data section to better describe how various types of users can easily share a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.31</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-23/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue in which confidence bands were not displaying on time plots. Improved the positioning of horizontal axis labels when exporting PowerPoint graphs. Crunch Automation Created DROP VARIABLES, which is a new Crunch Automation schema command that allows you to drop multiple variables in a dataset. Fixed the DISPLAY command so that it no longer overwrites other variable display attributes. Help desk and website improvements Added updated information about how to use Crunch Automation schema commands when writing a script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.30</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-16/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Changed how the N values are listed at the top of the marker bar in a time plot so that they always reflect the unweighted N value. Fixed an issue that occurred when time plots cannot be created in certain circumstances for a categorical variable with only one category. Added PowerPoint support so that &amp;lsquo;Min&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Max&amp;rsquo; Y-axis settings are now reflected in graph exports. Updated population estimates for &amp;ldquo;at least N of&amp;rdquo; filters so that they are now consistent when &amp;ldquo;complete cases&amp;rdquo; is turned off for the filter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.29</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-09/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue when hypothesis-testing shading was not being reflected in the &amp;lsquo;Mean&amp;rsquo; row when a column was selected for comparison. Added support for ascending/descending sorting of the labels column. Fixed an Excel export issue that occurred when creating filters through the &amp;lsquo;Filter by dropzone&amp;rsquo; that then resulted as an &amp;ldquo;on-the-fly&amp;rdquo; expression instead of the actual filter description. Fixed an issue that occurred when row labels could sometimes disappear when horizontal scrolling through a large bivariate analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.28</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-02/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Improved Confirmit integrations by streamlining the types of files they can accept. Fixed issue in which &amp;lsquo;sort by value&amp;rsquo; does not work properly if the display controller is set to display only subtotals. Crunch Automation Added the REPLACE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY FROM command, which allows you to convert in place a categorical array into a multiple response variable. See documentation for more information. Fixed an issue that occurred when combining CREATE CONVERT and UNSET NUMERIC VALUE commands in the same script for the same variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.27</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-26/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added functionality to prepend &amp;lsquo;Loop Names&amp;rsquo; to loop variables, which makes them work better in the UI and prevents clashes between variables. Fixed a bug in the Confirmit importer, which caused the variable name to be the same as the alias. Fixed a bug that caused integrated datasets to not have a working update dropdown. Made the following fixes and improvements: Negative differences now display properly if the checkbox &amp;lsquo;Empty rows/columns&amp;rsquo; in the display controller is deselected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.25-26</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-16/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Made the following fixes and improvements: Exports of scorecards now work properly. Variables can now be added to dashboard groups. A graph size now updates correctly when empty rows/columns are deselected. A multitable now loads properly when its definition includes a collection of variables that begins with a date/time variable. Display results no longer show &amp;rsquo;no data&amp;rsquo; values under certain conditions. The &amp;lsquo;Combine&amp;rsquo; categories panel no longer incorrectly includes subtotals and differences among the list of categories to combine, as well as no longer showing incorrect counts if subtotals or differences are defined in the variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.23-24</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-02/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed an issue that prevented the &amp;ldquo;Set comparison&amp;rdquo; button for hypothesis testing of tables from working properly when the option to show only categories is selected. Added the ability to include subtotals to multiple response variables (in early access for editors). Added support for deck export of numeric array variable cards. Made the following fixes: a multitable consisting of categorical variables now loads properly. a multitable with a multiple response column variable correctly displays means of numeric row variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.22</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-18/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Updated the Crunch app so that numeric arrays can be saved to a deck from the &amp;lsquo;Variable Summaries&amp;rsquo; view. Added options in the &amp;lsquo;Edit Slide/Tile&amp;rsquo; panel to allow you to hide the x-axis title and description for a graph. Fixed an issue when numeric arrays sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t display in the &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; view when a weight has been applied. Fixed an issue that sometimes caused the &amp;lsquo;Edit &amp;gt; Export Settings&amp;rsquo; page to not load properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.21</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-11/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added support for custom variables in SurveyMonkey integrations. Fixed an issue that prevented users from appending datasets with numeric arrays under certain conditions. Crunch Automation Made speed improvements to scripts that have multiple CREATE commands. Fixed an issue that occurred in CREATE MULTIPLE SELECTION command variables when referring to the generated subvariables in the same script. Help desk and website improvements Added new documentation for Decipher integrations (mappings and overview articles).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.20</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-04/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Improved backend support to allow creation of custom variables into views. Added a search field to the &amp;lsquo;Select&amp;rsquo; categories panel for time plots, which is displayed when the list of categories exceeds the available space in a view. Fixed a bug for integration updates when a subvariable with a duplicate name would cause a failure. Added the base size (N) to the tooltips above data points within vertical and horizontal bar graphs as well as pie graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.19</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-28/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed various Confirmit integration issues, including how responses appear when they contain newlines. Made the following Decipher integration improvements: Fixed an error when adding subvariables to an array when updating a &amp;lsquo;Decipher Integrated&amp;rsquo; dataset. Addressed issues with numeric arrays when updating datasets that are integrated with Decipher datasets. Improved how subtotals and differences are displayed by adding a boldface font in categorical-array variable summary cards. Added the ability to show weighted and unweighted bases on the tooltip when the measure is set to row percent in &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Multitable&amp;rsquo; modes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.18</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-21/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added the ability for organizations to route user questions and problems directly to personnel or online resources (blogs, knowledge base, help center, videos, etc) for any folder via the &amp;ldquo;Report an Issue&amp;rdquo; menu option. For example, you may want to configure a top-level regional folder to route user issues to your own, branded https://help.mycomany.com and configure a lower-level folder to route user questions to a specific email address like usa-questions@mycompany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.17</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-14/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Improved the time marker bar so that when you click the diamond symbol it now expands to display the margin of error when confidence bands are enabled in time plots. Improved the export settings functionality (for both deck and tab book exports), so that it now features a &amp;lsquo;bases&amp;rsquo; options for numeric measures. Added performance improvements and fixed various bugs to the export settings crosstab sections (tab book and edit slide).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.16</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-07/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added the ability to show the title and description for a column variable beneath the graph in edit preview and dashboards. Improved how datasets on a dashboard appear on a landing page so that the member&amp;rsquo;s panel no longer switches to a dashboard when closing it. Fixed a bug that improves how formulas for subtotals and differences are saved. Made numerous improvements to the Confirmit importer, including: Cleaned up the formatting of both folders, variable names, and descriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.15</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-30/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Improved the web app by displaying a descriptive error when an integration update fails. Improved the user experience when deleting a deck. Moved the N label in graphs to the bottom right and increased the font size. API Endpoints and API Reference Updated the API so that you can now add a suffix to your &amp;ldquo;join&amp;rdquo; API call, which allows the source variables to include a suffix to avoid conflicts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.14</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-23/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Released the time plot feature to wide access, so that &amp;rsquo;time periods&amp;rsquo; with no data at the beginning or end of a time range are now omitted from the horizontal axis — this is now dynamic as you add or remove categories. See the announcement and help documentation for more information. Fixed a bug that prevented datasets that are shared with users from appearing in search results. Improved how N values display on a time plot after selecting a categorical date entry on a group filter (in early access).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.13</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-16/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed a bug on the Decipher importer to instead show a full list when importing. Fixed a bug so that dashboards appear properly when switching tabs. Fixed a bug so that dropdown menus for individual dashboard tiles work properly. Improved PowerPoint graph exports to correctly show expected colors for negative values. Enhanced how standard deviations appear in tab book exports so that they correctly show the row variable as a numeric measure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.12</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-09/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Refactored the dataset importer and integrations in order to provide a more consistent and streamlined user experience. Fixed an issue with the importer that caused integrations to fail to render when there are too many surveys. Fixed an issue with variable sources and importer not working properly for Decipher integrations. Made various tweaks to Permissions Management and Dataset Importer panel UI to cause progressively loaded lists to render more consistently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.11</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-02/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Updated how descriptions are handled, which now allows them to extend to the entire width beneath a graph as needed. Changed the default to &amp;lsquo;aspect ratio&amp;rsquo; when rendering time plots in &amp;ldquo;Tables and graphs&amp;rdquo; mode (in early access). Improved search results by including: whether or not a dataset is a view, and for variable results, the type is now included. Fixed a bug so that now weighted numeric-array analyses are successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.10</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-26/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added feature to show values on a time plot when the user has Display &amp;gt; Values selected in the extended panel of the Display Controller (in early access). Updated horizontal bar graphs so that labels on an axis are no longer truncated. Added hint text to alert users who have any profile analyses saved to a deck, since these analyses cannot be exported via the &amp;ldquo;Export from deck&amp;rdquo; panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.9</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-19/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Reorganized the options on the Export settings panels for both slide exports and tab book exports for improved usability. Please refer to the help page for more information. Added a legend entry when exporting a single-measure numeric value to reflect what measure is being exported. Fixed the horizontal axis for time plots so that they no longer show empty time periods that might be present at either the beginning or the end of the categorical dates (in early access).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.8</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed case where missing columns in the response data can fail when importing a Qualtrics dataset. Adjusted y-axis min value so that it now be set to zero for the case of time plots. Fixed the extended panel when it opens from the display controller so that it no longer shrinks the displayed table or graph. Corrected how axis and tooltip labeling appears when displaying population estimates along the vertical axis of a time plot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.7</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-05/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed bug that prevented users from editing categories that are associated with an existing formula. Improved the ability to add scoring for Qualtrics variables in the Crunch app. Fixed bug that prevented you from exporting datasets in CSV format that explicitly included formulas as their variables. Fixed the ability to show categories more reliably at all screen sizes in the filter builder/categorical variable builder. Improved Confirmit integration to increase performance, fixed some bugs when multiple languages are in play, and reduced the dependency of the system on provided wsdl files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.6</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-26/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Fixed a bug that occurred when dragging a numeric variable onto a time plot as the &amp;lsquo;Cell&amp;rsquo; mean variable. Fixed issues that occurred when using the &amp;lsquo;Manage user&amp;rsquo; invite and edit forms. Changed the behavior of how notifications appear when a deck is closed. Added the ability to drag and drop numeric array variables with all other variables types in the &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; view. API Endpoints and API Reference Qualtrics is now supported as an integration type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.5</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-19/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added text input that allows you to write custom messages that are used when inviting users from the Members panel. Fixed an issue where stats don&amp;rsquo;t show up when using a filter builder on datasets where you do not have editing permissions. Made multiple response x 2 (MR x MR) analyses display correct N base value on graphs. Fixed a bug that occurred when inviting editors. Simplified options for dataset sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.5</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-19/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added text input that allows you to write custom messages that are used when inviting users from the Members panel. Fixed an issue where stats don&amp;rsquo;t show up when using a filter builder on datasets where you do not have editing permissions. Made multiple response x 2 (MR x MR) analyses display correct N base value on graphs. Fixed a bug that occurred when inviting editors. Simplified options for dataset sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.4</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Changes
Made the invite button available before the permission list is loaded. Added support for analyses involving a multiple response variable crossed with a numeric array variable. Bugfixes
Fixed timeplot, which was displaying wrong N count. Fixed tooltip value for Margin of Error. Fixed broken scrollbar behavior on filter builder in the categorical variable builder. SDKs (rCrunch, pyCrunch, and sCrunch) Improved sCrunch Backfill code. Crunch Automation Released the CREATE NUMERIC ARRAY command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.4</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Changes
Made the invite button available before the permission list is loaded. Added support for analyses involving a multiple response variable crossed with a numeric array variable. Bugfixes
Fixed timeplot, which was displaying wrong N count. Fixed tooltip value for Margin of Error. Fixed broken scrollbar behavior on filter builder in the categorical variable builder. SDKs (rCrunch, pyCrunch, and sCrunch) Improved sCrunch Backfill code. Crunch Automation Released the CREATE NUMERIC ARRAY command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.3</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-05/</guid>
      <description>Crunch Web Application Bug fixes:
Fixed broken pagination buttons on bar plots Fixed a bug that caused analysis titles and descriptions to display twice in dashboards view and edit tile panel. Made additional improvements to the categorical array builder, including the loading of saved expressions which include parentheses. Other changes:
Re-labeled column headers in Edit Categories panel. Hid &amp;ldquo;viztype&amp;rdquo; selector for numeric array analyses. API Endpoints and API Reference Improved search performance for folder-sorted search results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.3</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-05/</guid>
      <description>Crunch Web Application Bug fixes:
Fixed broken pagination buttons on bar plots Fixed a bug that caused analysis titles and descriptions to display twice in dashboards view and edit tile panel. Made additional improvements to the categorical array builder, including the loading of saved expressions which include parentheses. Other changes:
Re-labeled column headers in Edit Categories panel. Hid &amp;ldquo;viztype&amp;rdquo; selector for numeric array analyses. API Endpoints and API Reference Improved search performance for folder-sorted search results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.2</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-29/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app Refactor and performance enhancements to Search, making it easier for you to find things. Fix issue where dates could be shown incorrectly on project browser. We understand how frustrating it is when dates don&amp;rsquo;t appear correctly so we fixed this. Search behavior has now been changed to only search when you press return. Focusing on the control will open any previously obtained results. This will make search queries easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.2</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-29/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app Refactor and performance enhancements to Search, making it easier for you to find things. Fix issue where dates could be shown incorrectly on project browser. We understand how frustrating it is when dates don&amp;rsquo;t appear correctly so we fixed this. Search behavior has now been changed to only search when you press return. Focusing on the control will open any previously obtained results. This will make search queries easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.1</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-22/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app Provide you with the ability to customize table slide exports. See the help documentation for more information. Improve the &amp;lsquo;Margin of Error / Cell details&amp;rsquo; feature. See the help documentation for more information. Fix to the UI so that it now correctly shows the N range on a categorical array graph. API Endpoints and API Reference API endpoint documentation is live in its new home! See Crunch API Reference for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.1</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-22/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app Provide you with the ability to customize table slide exports. See the help documentation for more information. Improve the &amp;lsquo;Margin of Error / Cell details&amp;rsquo; feature. See the help documentation for more information. Fix to the UI so that it now correctly shows the N range on a categorical array graph. API Endpoints and API Reference API endpoint documentation is live in its new home! See Crunch API Reference for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capabilities</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 14:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/capabilities/</guid>
      <description>With Crunch.io, you can:
Analyze all your data in one place
Build crosstabs with a drag-and-drop
Add visualizations with one click
Export editable PowerPoint objects
Get rid of two-day turnarounds to answer questions
Create no-coding dashboards
Automate tracker wave updates of reports and dashboards</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deliver dashboards at scale, fast</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/automation/delivery-dasboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 15:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/automation/delivery-dasboard/</guid>
      <description>Design in the GUI. Automate with scripting Drag &amp;amp; drop to design Generate a script Copy the script to a new dataset or view Drag &amp;amp; drop to customize Deliver more dashboards
That anyone can easily edit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our mission</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/our-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 15:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/our-mission/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to empower teams to collaborate in a secure, online environment with a simple, self-service interface to quickly analyze, visualize, and deliver survey data. Power made simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our team</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/our-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 15:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/our-team/</guid>
      <description>While our origins are in the San Francisco Bay Area, we’ve been completely remote since day 1. Most of us are in the Americas, but we range from Australia to the Dominican Republic. We don’t just allow remote working. We embrace it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who we are</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 15:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>We’re a group of survey experts, market researchers, designers, and engineers.
We were frustrated by the current tools used to analyze, visualize, and deliver survey data. So, we built Crunch.io to bring easy self-service to survey data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No coding</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/773608182</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 14:45:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/player.vimeo.com/video/773608182</guid>
      <description>Your client will:
Filter, slice, dice and find insights
Export key tables and visualizations as editable PowerPoint objects, visually-appealing and presentation-ready, all by themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The new normal</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dashboards/the-new-normal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 14:45:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dashboards/the-new-normal/</guid>
      <description>Drag and drop to create visually-compelling dashboards. No programming or DP expertise required.
Add filters, tables, and graphs in just a few clicks
Resize, reorder, brand, and customize without coding
Broadly and quickly deploy dashboards with lower costs and fewer resources
Instantly create multiple dashboards for different audiences from one master dashboard with Crunch Views</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyze survey data with ease</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/analyze-survey-data-with-ease/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 16:37:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/analyze-survey-data-with-ease/</guid>
      <description>Unlike generic BI tools or Excel, Crunch.io was built to handle the unique characteristics of survey data.
Quickly apply or build:
Weighting Stats testing Advanced filters (nesting variables) Multiway or 3D tables Time series graphs Grids &amp;amp; scorecards </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalability</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/scalability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 16:37:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/scalability/</guid>
      <description> Instantly search across all your datasets Empower anyone to analyze or view findings Quickly and broadly deploy easy-to-build dashboards </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/simplicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 16:37:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/simplicity/</guid>
      <description> Analyze data with little or no training Create tables and charts Filter data Build dashboards in 5 minutes Empower customers and clients to answer their own questions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 16:37:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/speed/</guid>
      <description>The CrunchDB columnar database is purpose built to handle even your largest survey datasets with millions of respondents and thousands of variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tool</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 16:37:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/powerful-survey-analytics/tool/</guid>
      <description>Unlike generic BI tools, Crunch.io handles:
Weighting Missingness Stats testing Multiple response questions Advanced analytics </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy and Cookies Notice</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 17:09:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: May 31st, 2020 Protecting your privacy is very important to us at Crunch Cloud Analytics LLC (“Crunch”, “We”, “Us”, or “Our”), and we use our privacy and cookies notice to explain our practices regarding our collection and use of information that we receive through the online analytic services provided at www.crunch.io, and other related websites designated by Crunch (“Services”). This privacy and cookies notice applies to only those websites, services and applications included within our Services where this privacy notice is posted, and does not apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Deck Exports</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 10:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</guid>
      <description>We know that for many, PowerPoint slides remain central to delivering results and to paraphrase Mark Twain, &amp;ldquo;reports of PowerPoint&amp;rsquo;s death have been greatly exagerated&amp;rdquo;. Crunch has long offered exports of analyses and tab books to Excel files, which, in addition to their own value, enabled people to get results from Crunch to PowerPoint by copying a cell range from Excel into a slide. That’s a bit tedious, though, and we wanted to do better, which is why we are excited to announce that PowerPoint exports from Crunch are now available if you have ‘Early access’ enabled in the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Graphs Look Easy with ggplot2 and Tidy Evaluation</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/autoplot-with-tidyeval/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 12:12:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/autoplot-with-tidyeval/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch, one of the ways we try to make data exploration simple is by providing sensible default views that take into account the properties of your data and metadata. We&amp;rsquo;re in the process of releasing some plotting methods in our crplyr R package that define methods for ggplot2&amp;rsquo;s autoplot() function. autoplot() was the ideal approach for us to encapsulate the logic of how to &amp;ldquo;just do the right thing.&amp;rdquo; You can do the analysis you want, and it will make smart choices about how to display it with no additional input&amp;ndash;all of which you can control or override with additional ggplot2 layers, if you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API libraries</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/api-libraries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/api-libraries/</guid>
      <description>We have developed, and are always adding to, our R (RCrunch) and Python(PyCrunch) libraries, which perform many advanced uploading, cleaning, and analytics functions. But you don’t have to stop there, you can connect to Crunch and run any model you like, create bespoke visualizations, or even write your own packages. Crunch is a modern survey platform. The sky is the limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-focused/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-focused/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-pdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-pdf/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-read/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test-focused/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test-focused/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test-read/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test-view/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-test/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-testlocal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-testlocal/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference-view/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch API Reference</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:59:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/api/reference/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subtotals for Categorical Data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 13:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch, we are constantly searching for ways to help our customers&amp;mdash;and their clients&amp;mdash;gain insights from their data. A common task in the market-research world is to take data that is essentially a scale&amp;mdash;rate from 1 to 10, or an ordinal range of responses from &amp;ldquo;Strongly agree&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Strongly disagree&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;and collapse it into a smaller number of bins. For example, if you asked people to rate their preference on a scale of 1-10 you might want to see how the people who provide a rating between 1 and 5 compare to those who rated it between 6 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is designed to make data accessible to many different audiences that have varying needs, expectations, and technical abilities. Our browse and analyze views allow data owners and analysts to quickly explore and analyze interesting insights in potentially large, complex datasets. However, not everyone has time to explore a dataset&amp;mdash;some need to see key findings at a glance.
To meet this executive-type need, we&amp;rsquo;re introducing a new dashboard feature.
This dashboard provides a quick view of up to four analyses, right when you open a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Selenium with Docker for Consistent Testing</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/nightwatch-selenium-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/nightwatch-selenium-docker/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch we greatly value tests. We have unit tests, functional tests, and the stack wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be complete without end-to-end tests. Good tests allow us to update code quickly and confidently.
For our end-to-end testing we use Nightwatch.js, a JavaScript testing tool that uses Selenium to drive a browser to perform tests. Our goal is to be able to test our Python backend, our REST APIs, and the behavior of our JavaScript single-page application, using a real browser, running real code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developers As Users</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/devs-as-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 12:12:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/devs-as-users/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is designed to make it easy to manage and explore data, and it is particularly optimized for survey data. We natively support data types that are common in survey research, and it is also simple to do things like generate population weights and apply them automatically to all calculations. And the kinds of analyses and reports that are standard among researchers are easily selected and exported.
These features are great if you work at a research company, or in a marketing department, or otherwise work with surveys professionally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch R Package 1.18.0 Released</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/r-package-1-18-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 18:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/r-package-1-18-0/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just released version 1.18.0 of the Crunch R package. Current package users should see a message when they load the package instructing you how to update to the latest version. New users (or anyone) can install this latest release from CRAN with
install.packages(&amp;quot;crunch&amp;quot;) See the package website for further instructions.
Since the last CRAN release in June (1.17.0), some significant features have been added. A full list of changes can be found here, but here is an overview of the main additions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sentiment-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sentiment-analysis/</guid>
      <description>A wealth of information can be locked in text data. Our new “sentiment analysis” feature enables you to quantify and analyze just a bit of it: whether the text in question is on balance Positive, Neutral, or Negative — and then crosstab the derived sentiment variable just like any other variable to understand the variations among other groups in the dataset.
In the properties panel for text variables, you’ll notice the Classify button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refine your searches on Crunch</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/search-filters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 12:59:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/search-filters/</guid>
      <description>Search has been a part of Crunch from the beginning. In a system designed to house and share large volumes of data, the ability to quickly find the data that&amp;rsquo;s important right now is critical. We&amp;rsquo;re continually working to improve how data is indexed to make searching faster and more accurate, and we just added a couple new ways for you to refine your searches to get to what you are looking for faster and more easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>:bar_chart: New Header, New Font, New Graphs :chart_with_upwards_trend: </title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/visual-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 11:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/visual-updates/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been working on updating and improving the look of Crunch, and we wanted to take moment to call out a few of the recent improvements.
Let’s start at the top You may have noticed that we recently updated the Crunch header.
This new top bar provides a more unified look throughout the application, and allows us to move user settings, dataset settings, and project settings into unobtrusive and consistently located dropdown menus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deliver New Data When You’re Ready</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/draft-and-publish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/draft-and-publish/</guid>
      <description>Lately we’ve been focusing on ways to make it easier for data owners to manage data for their clients. After all, Crunch isn’t just for analyzing data, it’s a tool for making everything about delivering data to clients faster, smoother, and more powerful.
To that end, we’ve recently developed a draft and publish feature that allows data owners to make significant changes to data accessible to their clients with minimal interruption to how those clients interact with the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Travis-CI to Build Static Sites</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/building-the-blog-on-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 21:12:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/building-the-blog-on-travis/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch.io, we&amp;rsquo;re fervent believers in automation. If something requires a human to remember to do an extra manual step, it won&amp;rsquo;t happen consistently. We automate test running so that we don&amp;rsquo;t have to fix the same bug twice. We write code to do tedious tasks so that we can devote our mental energy to harder problems. We automate processes and policies so that developers don&amp;rsquo;t have remember the right things to do—the build and continuous-integration systems guide us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tab Book Improvements</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/tab-book-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/tab-book-improvements/</guid>
      <description>We first released the tab book feature a while back, and since then, we’ve collected a number of great suggestions for how to enrich the feature. Tab books produce a static set of tables out of many variables and put results in an Excel sheet, for offline use when you don’t need interactive features like new filters or different weights. Our recent release includes several of those enhancements, most of which are new options available to you in the “export tab book” panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create crunchbox</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/crunchbox/create-crunchbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/crunchbox/create-crunchbox/</guid>
      <description>Create a CrunchBox with a few clicks. Deliver it in a dashboard or webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise scalable</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/product/enterprise-scalable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/product/enterprise-scalable/</guid>
      <description> Everyone works on the same data, simultaneously, in the cloud. End the version control nightmare. Scale to all your datasets, even ones with millions of respondents (rows), and thousands of variables (columns) with sub-second response Analyze with sub-second response Instantly search across all your datasets. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opinion matters</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/marketing/opinion-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/marketing/opinion-matters/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powerful online analytics</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/product/powerful-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/product/powerful-analytics/</guid>
      <description> Empower everyone, from CMO to PhD, to analyze with an easy-to-use interface. Find insights faster. Stop pouring over hundreds of Excel tabs. No more 2-day turnarounds with DP to answer simple questions. Check awareness among female, millennial, Californians in 1 minute. Build an interactive dashboard in 5 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Result</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/search/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/search/search/</guid>
      <description>Nothing on this page will be visible. This file exists solely to respond to /search URL.
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trackers tamed</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/product/trackers-tamed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/product/trackers-tamed/</guid>
      <description>Track awareness across survey waves with one click. Automatically append tracking study waves. Plot data over time.
Learn more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try crunchbox</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/crunchbox/try-crunchbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/crunchbox/try-crunchbox/</guid>
      <description>This example allows you to explore American’s likelihood of voting. You can make crosstabs by a handful of Demographics, filter by two different groups, make tables, or charts, etc&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
