<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statistics on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/statistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statistics on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>See the margin of error and other helpful statistics in tables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</guid>
      <description>By using the new options panel revealed by clicking the three-dots icon in the display controller, users can choose which of these figures to display in the tooltip for table cells. The default statistics shown are the margin of error and unweighted base. Your chosen cell details are persisted as a user preference. For margin of error, you can also specify the number of decimal places you want to see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Click to set the comparison column for hypothesis tests</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/click-to-compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/click-to-compare/</guid>
      <description>Tables in the application now let you set a column as the basis of comparison, shading the table to show which other columns are higher or lower than the reference column, and to what level of statistical significance. The test is a two-tailed t test comparing each column proportion in turn to the proportion in the reference column. In a multitable, the test is conducted between categories within each column variable, and not across column variables.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
