<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analysis on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analysis on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:00:10 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Greater flexibility to customize exports of tables from decks and dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-export-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:00:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-export-settings/</guid>
      <description>Back in September, we added a variety of advanced calculations to include in tab books (exported multitables) and other options to customize the exported tables. We&amp;rsquo;ve now added these same customization options to tables saved to (and exported from) the deck.
This can be helpful if you need to:
Show more than one measure (percentages, counts, indices, Z-scores, population estimates) at once, or
Have additional elements or measures included in your exports, such as pairwise comparison letters (ABCD), standard deviations, standard errors, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greater flexibility to customize tab books</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 16:12:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</guid>
      <description>You can now choose a variety of advanced calculations to include in tab books (exported multitables) and other options to customize the exported tables. Table cells can now contain estimates of standard deviation and standard error, and column summaries can include the median of numeric values as well as the standard deviation for the column and standard error of the mean. Pairwise column significance tests can be conducted at the standard 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easily create and recombine categorical arrays and multiple response variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-multiple-response-cat-array-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:34:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-multiple-response-cat-array-builder/</guid>
      <description>Array variables allow you to analyze together a set of variables that share a common structure and theme. For example, surveys often ask respondents to use a common scale to rate or respond to different prompts, sometimes in a grid, all sharing a common set of response categories. When analyzing the data, a categorical array variable lets users see all the items together. This structure allows users to easily compare lists of brands against a common set of attributes, or compare a set of statements against a common agreement scale — something that is much harder to do with distinct categorical variables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom color palettes for your saved analyses</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 12:14:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been possible for some time to set custom colors for saved analyses in Crunch, but it&amp;rsquo;s been necessary to do this on a one-by-one basis which can be laborious and open to inconsistency. We now offer the ability to create custom color palettes, defined at the organization level, at folder levels, or both, which apply your chosen colors to newly created analyses as well as offering alternatives (e.g. for scales) that can be applied easily, as needed for particular analyses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Deck Exports</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 10:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</guid>
      <description>We know that for many, PowerPoint slides remain central to delivering results and to paraphrase Mark Twain, &amp;ldquo;reports of PowerPoint&amp;rsquo;s death have been greatly exagerated&amp;rdquo;. Crunch has long offered exports of analyses and tab books to Excel files, which, in addition to their own value, enabled people to get results from Crunch to PowerPoint by copying a cell range from Excel into a slide. That’s a bit tedious, though, and we wanted to do better, which is why we are excited to announce that PowerPoint exports from Crunch are now available if you have ‘Early access’ enabled in the app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subtotals for Categorical Data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 13:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch, we are constantly searching for ways to help our customers&amp;mdash;and their clients&amp;mdash;gain insights from their data. A common task in the market-research world is to take data that is essentially a scale&amp;mdash;rate from 1 to 10, or an ordinal range of responses from &amp;ldquo;Strongly agree&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Strongly disagree&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;and collapse it into a smaller number of bins. For example, if you asked people to rate their preference on a scale of 1-10 you might want to see how the people who provide a rating between 1 and 5 compare to those who rated it between 6 and 10.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
