<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Analysis on Data, Smarter.</title>
    <link>/tags/analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Analysis on Data, Smarter.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 10:20:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Deck Exports</title>
      <link>/dev/features/pptx-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 10:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dev/features/pptx-exports/</guid>
      <description>We know that for many, data analysis isn’t complete until the results are in a PowerPoint slide deck. Crunch has long offered exports of analyses and tab books to Excel files, which, in addition to their own value, enabled people to get results from Crunch to PowerPoint by copying a cell range from Excel into a slide. That’s a bit tedious, though, and we wanted to do better, which is why we are excited to announce that PowerPoint exports from Crunch are now available if you have ‘Early access’ enabled in the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subtotals for Categorical Data</title>
      <link>/dev/features/subtotals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 13:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dev/features/subtotals/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch, we are constantly searching for ways to help our customers&amp;mdash;and their clients&amp;mdash;gain insights from their data. A common task in the market-research world is to take data that is essentially a scale&amp;mdash;rate from 1 to 10, or an ordinal range of responses from &amp;ldquo;Strongly agree&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Strongly disagree&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;and collapse it into a smaller number of bins. For example, if you asked people to rate their preference on a scale of 1-10 you might want to see how the people who provide a rating between 1 and 5 compare to those who rated it between 6 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>