<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Confidence Intervals on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/confidence-intervals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Confidence Intervals on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:01:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/confidence-intervals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bringing the Enhanced Bar Plot capabilities to Grouped Bar Plots</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-grouped-bar-plots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-grouped-bar-plots/</guid>
      <description>Why This Matters Understanding your survey data is crucial to making informed decisions. While Crunch has always been at the forefront of providing survey analytics tools, we believe that data visualization can play a more prominent role in the research process. That’s why we&amp;rsquo;ve revamped our grouped bar plots to bring you an even more intuitive and insightful experience, bringing them in line with the enhancements already brought to univariate bar plots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Enhanced Bar Plots in Crunch – Best Practice in Survey Data Visualization</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-bar-plots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 15:29:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-bar-plots/</guid>
      <description>We’re thrilled to announce a significant update that will enhance the way you visualize and interpret your survey data. Our Upgraded Bar Plots have been redesigned with a cleaner layout, more easily readable text, and now feature the display of confidence intervals.&#xA;Why This Matters Understanding your survey data is crucial to making informed decisions. While Crunch has always been at the forefront of providing survey analytics tools, we believe that data visualization can play a more prominent role in the research process.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
