<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crunch.io Release Notes</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/</link>
    <description>Developer notes, bug fixes, documentation, API, and application changes.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.37</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-10-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-10-04/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Made the following fixes:  KPIs are now correctly set to a table cell when viewing a multiple response analysis. Category hiding and color assignment are now correctly reflected in a dashboard tile. Category labels that have been renamed using &amp;lsquo;Edit tile&amp;rsquo; now show the correct label (vs. the original label) when sorting in a dashboard tile. A properly formatted table now appears when switching between &amp;lsquo;Multitable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; graphs&amp;rsquo; views.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the following fixes:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;KPIs are now correctly set to a table cell when viewing a multiple response analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category hiding and color assignment are now correctly reflected in a dashboard tile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category labels that have been renamed using &amp;lsquo;Edit tile&amp;rsquo; now show the correct label (vs. the original label) when sorting in a dashboard tile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A properly formatted table now appears when switching between &amp;lsquo;Multitable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; graphs&amp;rsquo; views.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dashboard tiles that have a date/time variable in the analysis now load properly when the application of the group filters yielded &amp;lsquo;N=0&amp;rsquo; for that tile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability for the user to change the visualization type to a bar graph within the &amp;lsquo;Edit&amp;rsquo; panel (in situations when the user selects the &amp;lsquo;Show means&amp;rsquo; option for a univariate categorical variable in a saved table analysis).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that occurred when using certain filers in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057819011-OVERWRITE-VALUES-command&#34;&gt;OVERWRITE VALUES command&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability when using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042458431-CREATE-CATEGORICAL-CUT-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CUT command&lt;/a&gt; to allow numeric arrays, which then create categorical arrays as the output.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new information to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040072292-Adding-your-Branding-to-Crunch&#34;&gt;Adding your Branding to Crunch&lt;/a&gt; about how to customize the &amp;lsquo;Report an Issue link&amp;rsquo; to allow users to ask questions to someone on your team who is most familiar with your data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.36</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-27/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Made the following color assignment corrections:  in deck analyses that include a multiple response variable with subtotals. in a categorical variable that has subtotals/differences defined for it.   Added an &amp;lsquo;Insufficient Data&amp;rsquo; message on a tile, which appears when dashboard tiles have no results due to group filtering. Added the ability to drag tiles to a new location on the current dashboard tab by using only one drag-and-drop action.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the following color assignment corrections:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in deck analyses that include a multiple response variable with subtotals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in a categorical variable that has subtotals/differences defined for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added an &amp;lsquo;Insufficient Data&amp;rsquo; message on a tile, which appears when dashboard tiles have no results due to group filtering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to drag tiles to a new location on the current dashboard tab by using only one drag-and-drop action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added bar graph support in situations where the &amp;lsquo;Show means&amp;rsquo; option has been selected for a univariate categorical variable in the &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; graphs&amp;rsquo; view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue in which the view within &amp;lsquo;Edit preview&amp;rsquo; was not responding to the change after sorting the direction for a sorted univariate analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4407236789901-DROP-VARIABLES-command&#34;&gt;DROP VARIABLES command&lt;/a&gt; to allow a larger number of variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a new article about &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4409897907981-Numeric-Arrays&#34;&gt;Numeric Arrays&lt;/a&gt;, which is a new variable type that enables you to work efficiently with groups of numeric variables that are related.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.35</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-20/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed an issue that occurred when a tab on a dashboard tile was not allowing the user to change the selection. Improved the behavior in the &amp;lsquo;Dashboards Group&amp;rsquo; panel in situations when one or more of the filter variables have been deleted from the dataset. Fixed an issue that occurred when selecting a category in the &amp;lsquo;Dashboard Group&amp;rsquo; panel that sometimes did not reflect in the rendering of the dashboard.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when a tab on a dashboard tile was not allowing the user to change the selection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the behavior in the &amp;lsquo;Dashboards Group&amp;rsquo; panel in situations when one or more of the filter variables have been deleted from the dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when selecting a category in the &amp;lsquo;Dashboard Group&amp;rsquo; panel that sometimes did not reflect in the rendering of the dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4403966631309-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Confirmit-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;Confirmit integrations&lt;/a&gt; when response data was smaller than expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corrected an issue that occurred when a dashboard tile no longer reflects the column selected for hypothesis testing comparisons after changing the selection in the tab pulldown within that tile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to remove a stale reference in dashboard &amp;lsquo;groups&amp;rsquo; when a variable has been deleted from the dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to download a Crunch Automaton script (a series of &lt;code&gt;organize&lt;/code&gt; commands) reflecting the current variable folder structure from the &amp;lsquo;Edit variables&amp;rsquo; interface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API endpoints and API reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated an endpoint that allows users to &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#get-/datasets/-dataset_id-/folders/script/&#34;&gt;generate a Crunch Automation script&lt;/a&gt; containing &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042457291-ORGANIZE-command&#34;&gt;ORGANIZE commands&lt;/a&gt; that are necessary in order to recreate the current dataset&amp;rsquo;s variables organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that occurred when parsing Crunch Automation comparisons to &lt;code&gt;NULL&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.34</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-13/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed an issue that occurred when a filter is created by dragging a variable from &amp;ldquo;My variables&amp;rdquo; to the filter zone so that it now works correctly. Fixed an issue that occurred when an unexpected format for the filter definition sometimes causes a dashboard tile to not load properly.  API endpoints and API reference  Updated the folder endpoint to obtain the variable organization script so that it now returns a shoji:view as default, but will return a plain text response if requested with the Accept HTTP header text/plain.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when a filter is created by dragging a variable from &amp;ldquo;My variables&amp;rdquo; to the filter zone so that it now works correctly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when an unexpected format for the filter definition sometimes causes a dashboard tile to not load properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API endpoints and API reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#get-/datasets/-dataset_id-/folders/script/&#34;&gt;folder endpoint&lt;/a&gt; to obtain the variable organization script so that it now returns a &lt;code&gt;shoji:view&lt;/code&gt; as default, but will return a plain text response if requested with the &lt;code&gt;Accept&lt;/code&gt; HTTP header &lt;code&gt;text/plain&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#post-/datasets/-dataset_view_id-/view_preview/&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; about a new API endpoint that allows you to do a dependency check for proposed changes to dataset view definitions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed two bugs for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042247331-RENAME-command&#34;&gt;RENAME command&lt;/a&gt; when working with arrays and their subvariables within the same script.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.33</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-09-06/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Updated the Crunch UI so that deck slides and dashboard tiles are correctly weighted with the updated variable when a weight variable is deleted and re-created with the same alias. Improved Qualtrics integrations, which now support embedded data. Updated how &amp;lsquo;Unweighted N / All&amp;rsquo; column values appear so that they now correctly display in multitable view when the row variable is a categorical array. Added the ability to allow a dataset editor to reorder the slides of a deck that are owned by another user.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the Crunch UI so that deck slides and dashboard tiles are correctly weighted with the updated variable when a weight variable is deleted and re-created with the same alias.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved Qualtrics integrations, which now support embedded data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated how &amp;lsquo;Unweighted N / All&amp;rsquo; column values appear so that they now correctly display in multitable view when the row variable is a categorical array.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to allow a dataset editor to reorder the slides of a deck that are owned by another user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue in which an exported tab book yields an incorrectly arranged output if the multitable includes hidden elements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved support for hypothesis-testing shading when empty rows/columns are not displayed and a column is selected for comparison.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhanced filter usage by allowing direct exports of dataset row-level data in situations that involve &amp;ldquo;at least N of&amp;rdquo; expressions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040297192-Scorecards-your-flexible-summary-grid&#34;&gt;Scorecards: your flexible summary grid&lt;/a&gt; article with new information on how to create a scorecard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057226852-Time-series-analysis-with-time-plots&#34;&gt;Time series analysis with time plots&lt;/a&gt; article with additional information on how to work with Date/Time variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.32</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-30/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Updated data exports so that hidden multiple response subtotals are no longer included. Improved the &amp;lsquo;Select Categories&amp;rsquo; panel for a time plot so that it now displays multiple response subtotals in the correct order.  Help desk and website improvements  Created a new article that describes how to use a CSV + JSON metadata document to automate the setup of a dataset. Organized the Sharing Data section to better describe how various types of users can easily share a dataset.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated data exports so that hidden multiple response subtotals are no longer included.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the &amp;lsquo;Select Categories&amp;rsquo; panel for a time plot so that it now displays multiple response subtotals in the correct order.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a new article that describes &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4407992870925-Setting-up-a-dataset-from-CSV-datafile-JSON-metadata-description-document&#34;&gt;how to use a CSV + JSON metadata document&lt;/a&gt; to automate the setup of a dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/sections/360008205352-Sharing-Data&#34;&gt;Sharing Data&lt;/a&gt; section to better describe how various types of users can easily share a dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040119051-How-to-import-from-Decipher-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;How to import from Decipher into Crunch&lt;/a&gt; article with new information about Decipher permissions and using the Crunch API.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.31</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-23/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed an issue in which confidence bands were not displaying on time plots. Improved the positioning of horizontal axis labels when exporting PowerPoint graphs.  Crunch Automation  Created DROP VARIABLES, which is a new Crunch Automation schema command that allows you to drop multiple variables in a dataset. Fixed the DISPLAY command so that it no longer overwrites other variable display attributes.  Help desk and website improvements  Added updated information about how to use Crunch Automation schema commands when writing a script.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue in which confidence bands were not displaying on time plots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the positioning of horizontal axis labels when exporting PowerPoint graphs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4407236789901-DROP-VARIABLES-command&#34;&gt;DROP VARIABLES&lt;/a&gt;, which is a new Crunch Automation schema command that allows you to drop multiple variables in a dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038692-DISPLAY-command&#34;&gt;DISPLAY command&lt;/a&gt; so that it no longer overwrites other variable display attributes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added updated information about how to use &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292-Crunch-Automation-basics#toc1&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation schema commands&lt;/a&gt; when writing a script.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057226852-Time-series-analysis-with-time-plots&#34;&gt;Time series analysis with time plots&lt;/a&gt; article, which describes how to use the new time plot visualizations. These are now enabled for date-time variables for Early Access users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the following articles with new information about the various tables, graphs, and charts that are now available to Crunch users:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040932251-Customizing-a-Table-or-Graph&#34;&gt;Customizing a Table or Graph&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360039907171-What-chart-types-are-available-&#34;&gt;What chart types are available?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360039693692-Cool-tables-and-graphs&#34;&gt;Cool tables and graphs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040498472-Creating-Tables-Graphs-and-Maps&#34;&gt;Creating Tables, Graphs, and Maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.30</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-16/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Changed how the N values are listed at the top of the marker bar in a time plot so that they always reflect the unweighted N value. Fixed an issue that occurred when time plots cannot be created in certain circumstances for a categorical variable with only one category. Added PowerPoint support so that &amp;lsquo;Min&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Max&amp;rsquo; Y-axis settings are now reflected in graph exports. Updated population estimates for &amp;ldquo;at least N of&amp;rdquo; filters so that they are now consistent when &amp;ldquo;complete cases&amp;rdquo; is turned off for the filter.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changed how the N values are listed at the top of the marker bar in a time plot so that they always reflect the unweighted N value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when time plots cannot be created in certain circumstances for a categorical variable with only one category.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added PowerPoint support so that &amp;lsquo;Min&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Max&amp;rsquo; Y-axis settings are now reflected in graph exports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated population estimates for &amp;ldquo;at least N of&amp;rdquo; filters so that they are now consistent when &amp;ldquo;complete cases&amp;rdquo; is turned off for the filter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#patch-/projects/-project_id-/&#34;&gt;/projects&lt;/a&gt; path, which changes project settings and allows you to move datasets and sub-projects into it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed the &lt;code&gt;/datasets/{id}/folders/trash/&lt;/code&gt; endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unmaterialize materialized commands — went back to creating derived variables in automation &lt;code&gt;CREATE VARIABLE&lt;/code&gt; commands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.29</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-09/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed an issue when hypothesis-testing shading was not being reflected in the &amp;lsquo;Mean&amp;rsquo; row when a column was selected for comparison. Added support for ascending/descending sorting of the labels column. Fixed an Excel export issue that occurred when creating filters through the &amp;lsquo;Filter by dropzone&amp;rsquo; that then resulted as an &amp;ldquo;on-the-fly&amp;rdquo; expression instead of the actual filter description. Fixed an issue that occurred when row labels could sometimes disappear when horizontal scrolling through a large bivariate analysis.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue when hypothesis-testing shading was not being reflected in the &amp;lsquo;Mean&amp;rsquo; row when a column was selected for comparison.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support for ascending/descending sorting of the labels column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an Excel export issue that occurred when creating filters through the &amp;lsquo;Filter by dropzone&amp;rsquo; that then resulted as an &amp;ldquo;on-the-fly&amp;rdquo; expression instead of the actual filter description.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when row labels could sometimes disappear when horizontal scrolling through a large bivariate analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360045887531-Stacking-a-dataset-using-R&#34;&gt;Stacking a dataset using R&lt;/a&gt; article with new information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.28</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-08-02/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Improved Confirmit integrations by streamlining the types of files they can accept. Fixed issue in which &amp;lsquo;sort by value&amp;rsquo; does not work properly if the display controller is set to display only subtotals.  Crunch Automation  Added the REPLACE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY FROM command, which allows you to convert in place a categorical array into a multiple response variable. See documentation for more information. Fixed an issue that occurred when combining CREATE CONVERT and UNSET NUMERIC VALUE commands in the same script for the same variable.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4403966631309-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Confirmit-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;Confirmit integrations&lt;/a&gt; by streamlining the types of files they can accept.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed issue in which &amp;lsquo;sort by value&amp;rsquo; does not work properly if the display controller is set to display only subtotals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the REPLACE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY FROM command, which allows you to convert in place a categorical array into a multiple response variable. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4406071596301-REPLACE-MULTIPLE-DICHOTOMY-FROM-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when combining &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360047136371-CREATE-CONVERT-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CONVERT&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360049589551-UNSET-NUMERIC-VALUE-command&#34;&gt;UNSET NUMERIC VALUE&lt;/a&gt; commands in the same script for the same variable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.27</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-26/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Added functionality to prepend &amp;lsquo;Loop Names&amp;rsquo; to loop variables, which makes them work better in the UI and prevents clashes between variables. Fixed a bug in the Confirmit importer, which caused the variable name to be the same as the alias. Fixed a bug that caused integrated datasets to not have a working update dropdown. Made the following fixes and improvements:  Negative differences now display properly if the checkbox &amp;lsquo;Empty rows/columns&amp;rsquo; in the display controller is deselected.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added functionality to prepend &amp;lsquo;Loop Names&amp;rsquo; to loop variables, which makes them work better in the UI and prevents clashes between variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4403966631309-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Confirmit-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;Confirmit importer&lt;/a&gt;, which caused the variable name to be the same as the alias.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused integrated datasets to not have a working update dropdown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the following fixes and improvements:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negative differences now display properly if the checkbox &amp;lsquo;Empty rows/columns&amp;rsquo; in the display controller is deselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displayed categories now correctly match the selected list of categories in dashboard time plots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pairwise comparisons now appear correctly for an analysis that has a multiple response variable in the column position (in cases where the multiple response variable included at least one subtotal).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The UI now works properly when &amp;lsquo;Missing&amp;rsquo; categories are positioned anywhere outside of the bottom of the category list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The anchoring of subtotals at the bottom of the list of categories now correctly renders the relevant variable summary card.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tooltips above table cells now display the correct information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The properties panel for a categorical array now displays correct information when one or more subtotals or differences were defined on the categories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &amp;lsquo;Set comparison&amp;rsquo; hypothesis testing option is now available in cases where subvariables are in the column position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created new &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4405014460301-SPSS-datafile-specifications&#34;&gt;SPSS datafile specifications&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created new &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4405077579405-Cleaning-relabeling-categories&#34;&gt;Cleaning/relabeling categories&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new info to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041300531-Dataset-Level-User-Access&#34;&gt;Dataset Level User Access&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044362492-The-Definitive-Guide-to-Importing-and-Preparing-Data&#34;&gt;Definitive Guide to Importing and Preparing Data&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360045930891-Setting-category-numeric-values-dates&#34;&gt;Setting category numeric values &amp;amp; dates&lt;/a&gt; with new information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added Crunch Automation commands to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360059213452-Category-Differences&#34;&gt;Category Differences&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more info and links to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044737751-Multidimensional-Analysis&#34;&gt;Multidimensional Analysis&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.25-26</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-16/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Made the following fixes and improvements:  Exports of scorecards now work properly. Variables can now be added to dashboard groups. A graph size now updates correctly when empty rows/columns are deselected. A multitable now loads properly when its definition includes a collection of variables that begins with a date/time variable. Display results no longer show &amp;lsquo;no data&amp;rsquo; values under certain conditions. The &amp;lsquo;Combine&amp;rsquo; categories panel no longer incorrectly includes subtotals and differences among the list of categories to combine, as well as no longer showing incorrect counts if subtotals or differences are defined in the variable.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the following fixes and improvements:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exports of scorecards now work properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Variables can now be added to dashboard groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A graph size now updates correctly when empty rows/columns are deselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A multitable now loads properly when its definition includes a collection of variables that begins with a date/time variable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display results no longer show &amp;lsquo;no data&amp;rsquo; values under certain conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &amp;lsquo;Combine&amp;rsquo; categories panel no longer incorrectly includes subtotals and differences among the list of categories to combine, as well as no longer showing incorrect counts if subtotals or differences are defined in the variable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Values now properly display on bar graphs when using the &amp;lsquo;Show values&amp;rsquo; setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Variable cards from a saved deck analysis now open and render properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support for third-party integrations when deleting a variable from a datasource so that it also removes it from the Crunch dataset if no other variables depend on the deleted variable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &amp;lsquo;Set Comparison&amp;rsquo; option so that it no longer displays if the measure is set to row percent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed left and right browsing arrows on &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Multitable&amp;rsquo; views.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to automatically sort graph categories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enabled vertical and horizontal bar graphs as visualization options for means analyses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved search performance when filtering a search by folder ID.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enabled scorecards to display multiple response subtotals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292-Crunch-Automation-basics#toc16&#34;&gt;REPLACE commands&lt;/a&gt; when using function expansions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038692-DISPLAY-command&#34;&gt;DISPLAY command&lt;/a&gt; by adding the ability to add nets to multiple response variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added comprehensive survey metadata mapping information to the following articles:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4403966631309-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Confirmit-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;Confirmit&lt;/a&gt; — updated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360062142812-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Decipher-into-Crunch#toc4&#34;&gt;Decipher&lt;/a&gt; — updated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4404356327693-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-SurveyMonkey-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;SurveyMonkey&lt;/a&gt; — &lt;em&gt;New!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360039306152-Tables-and-charts-with-drag-and-drop&#34;&gt;Tables and charts with drag-and-drop&lt;/a&gt; article with new information about how to sort tables and graphs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.23-24</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-07-02/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed an issue that prevented the &amp;ldquo;Set comparison&amp;rdquo; button for hypothesis testing of tables from working properly when the option to show only categories is selected. Added the ability to include subtotals to multiple response variables (in early access for editors). Added support for deck export of numeric array variable cards. Made the following fixes:  a multitable consisting of categorical variables now loads properly. a multitable with a multiple response column variable correctly displays means of numeric row variables.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented the &amp;ldquo;Set comparison&amp;rdquo; button for hypothesis testing of tables from working properly when the option to show only categories is selected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to include subtotals to multiple response variables (in early access for editors).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support for deck export of numeric array variable cards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the following fixes:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a multitable consisting of categorical variables now loads properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a multitable with a multiple response column variable correctly displays means of numeric row variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;differences now display in the &amp;lsquo;Edit slide/title&amp;rsquo; preview for categorical arrays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hiding column categories now works in the &amp;lsquo;Edit Categories&amp;rsquo; tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more support for both Confirmit and Decipher integrations (see help desk articles below for more information).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed a meaningless value in the intersection between the weighted/unweighted &amp;lsquo;rows and mean&amp;rsquo; column of exports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed multiple issues in the dashboard &amp;lsquo;groups&amp;rsquo; panel that prevented removing or adding them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed rare behavior that causes some export settings to fail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made more speed improvements to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360049589551-UNSET-NUMERIC-VALUE-command&#34;&gt;UNSET NUMERIC VALUE command&lt;/a&gt; when using numerous variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038132-CHANGE-command&#34;&gt;CHANGE command&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;code&gt;LABELS&lt;/code&gt;)  so that it can use functions alongside the explicit list of labels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360050364772-Category-Subtotals&#34;&gt;Category Subtotals&lt;/a&gt; article with new information about how to add subtotals to multiple response variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a new article that describes how &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/4403966631309-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Confirmit-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;metadata maps from Confirmit&lt;/a&gt; into Crunch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new information about how &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360062142812-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Decipher-into-Crunch#toc4&#34;&gt;Decipher logic elements (&amp;ldquo;Loops&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/a&gt; map into Crunch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360061204751-Crunch-importers-overview&#34;&gt;feature matrix&lt;/a&gt; in the Crunch importers overview article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360045631232-Nets-on-a-multiple-response-variable&#34;&gt;Nets on a multiple response variable&lt;/a&gt; article with new information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.22</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-18/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Updated the Crunch app so that numeric arrays can be saved to a deck from the &amp;lsquo;Variable Summaries&amp;rsquo; view. Added options in the &amp;lsquo;Edit Slide/Tile&amp;rsquo; panel to allow you to hide the x-axis title and description for a graph. Fixed an issue when numeric arrays sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t display in the &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; view when a weight has been applied. Fixed an issue that sometimes caused the &amp;lsquo;Edit &amp;gt; Export Settings&amp;rsquo; page to not load properly.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the Crunch app so that numeric arrays can be saved to a deck from the &amp;lsquo;Variable Summaries&amp;rsquo; view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added options in the &amp;lsquo;Edit Slide/Tile&amp;rsquo; panel to allow you to hide the x-axis title and description for a graph.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue when numeric arrays sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t display in the &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; view when a weight has been applied.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that sometimes caused the &amp;lsquo;Edit &amp;gt; Export Settings&amp;rsquo; page to not load properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removed the extra scrollbar from the numeric array summary graph.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changed the default measure to &amp;ldquo;column percent&amp;rdquo; within the resulting table when removing the variable in a &amp;lsquo;table of means&amp;rsquo; (in tables &amp;amp; graphs mode).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support in the Edit panel to switch between &amp;lsquo;Mean and Sum&amp;rsquo; measures for a numeric array analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated export handling to reflect a dash in the intersection of the &amp;lsquo;Unweighted/Weighted N&amp;rsquo; row(s) and the &amp;lsquo;Mean&amp;rsquo; column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increased the length of the maximum subvariable name, which is displayed in the numeric array summary axis label.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made several improvements, including how Crunch Automation commands create multiple kinds of array variables as well as fixed a bug that occurred when parsing automation expressions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360047136371-CREATE-CONVERT-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CONVERT command&lt;/a&gt; to allow you to convert categorical array variables into numeric arrays (converts them to &lt;code&gt;NUMERIC&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added clarifying information to both the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360045628752-Subtotals-nets-on-a-categorical-variable-or-array&#34;&gt;Subtotals (&amp;lsquo;nets&amp;rsquo;) on a categorical variable or array&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360050829991-How-to-add-subtotals-to-a-variable&#34;&gt;How to add subtotals to a variable&lt;/a&gt; articles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360039980612-How-to-find-a-dataset&#34;&gt;How to find a dataset&lt;/a&gt; with new information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.21</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-11/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Added support for custom variables in SurveyMonkey integrations. Fixed an issue that prevented users from appending datasets with numeric arrays under certain conditions.  Crunch Automation  Made speed improvements to scripts that have multiple CREATE commands. Fixed an issue that occurred in CREATE MULTIPLE SELECTION command variables when referring to the generated subvariables in the same script.  Help desk and website improvements  Added new documentation for Decipher integrations (mappings and overview articles).</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support for custom variables in SurveyMonkey integrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented users from appending datasets with numeric arrays under certain conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made speed improvements to scripts that have multiple &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/sections/360010677071-Crunch-Automation-commands&#34;&gt;CREATE commands&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred in &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044079971-CREATE-MULTIPLE-SELECTION-command&#34;&gt;CREATE MULTIPLE SELECTION command&lt;/a&gt; variables when referring to the generated subvariables in the same script.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new documentation for Decipher integrations (&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360062142812-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Decipher-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;mappings&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360061204751-Crunch-importers-overview&#34;&gt;overview&lt;/a&gt; articles).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360052195131-The-Definitive-Guide-to-Tracking&#34;&gt;Definitive Guide to Tracking&lt;/a&gt; article with new information about discrete waves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.20</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-06-04/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Improved backend support to allow creation of custom variables into views. Added a search field to the &amp;lsquo;Select&amp;rsquo; categories panel for time plots, which is displayed when the list of categories exceeds the available space in a view. Fixed a bug for integration updates when a subvariable with a duplicate name would cause a failure. Added the base size (N) to the tooltips above data points within vertical and horizontal bar graphs as well as pie graphs.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved backend support to allow creation of custom variables into views.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a search field to the &amp;lsquo;Select&amp;rsquo; categories panel for time plots, which is displayed when the list of categories exceeds the available space in a view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug for integration updates when a subvariable with a duplicate name would cause a failure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the base size (N) to the tooltips above data points within vertical and horizontal bar graphs as well as pie graphs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented export settings from being opened.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhanced how calculations are performed for population estimates when a filter is applied: in a scenario where that filter consists of a single wave of a categorical date variable, that wave is now assumed to represent the entire population.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the base value to the lower right of univariate graphs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corrected a scenario in which Numeric Array analyses sometimes are not able to be added to a deck.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made improvements when running scripts that include multiple &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042457091-CREATE-FILTER-command&#34;&gt;CREATE FILTER command&lt;/a&gt;s, which increases performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that occurred when attempting to delete a script that creates variables that are later used in the dataset&amp;rsquo;s exclusion filter: this will now show a conflict.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.19</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-28/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed various Confirmit integration issues, including how responses appear when they contain newlines. Made the following Decipher integration improvements:  Fixed an error when adding subvariables to an array when updating a &amp;lsquo;Decipher Integrated&amp;rsquo; dataset. Addressed issues with numeric arrays when updating datasets that are integrated with Decipher datasets.   Improved how subtotals and differences are displayed by adding a boldface font in categorical-array variable summary cards.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed various Confirmit integration issues, including how responses appear when they contain newlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the following Decipher integration improvements:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an error when adding subvariables to an array when updating a &amp;lsquo;Decipher Integrated&amp;rsquo; dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Addressed issues with numeric arrays when updating datasets that are integrated with Decipher datasets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how subtotals and differences are displayed by adding a boldface font in categorical-array variable summary cards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to show weighted and unweighted bases on the tooltip when the measure is set to row percent in &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Multitable&amp;rsquo; modes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how variable summary cards appear for numeric arrays so that they now correctly reflect filtered values after applying filters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made numerous QA edits to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/&#34;&gt;Crunch API reference&lt;/a&gt; docs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more information about filter parameters when using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#get-/search/&#34;&gt;Cross-dataset search endpoint&lt;/a&gt; as well as the ability for users to use an &amp;ldquo;all terms&amp;rdquo; parameter to improve search results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved performance by 12% when when filtering the root folder on large dataset search queries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#patch-/datasets/-dataset_id-/&#34;&gt;API documentation&lt;/a&gt; that describes how to copy views from one dataset to another.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made speed improvements to scripts that have multiple &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038692-DISPLAY-command&#34;&gt;DISPLAY,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038132-CHANGE-command&#34;&gt;CHANGE&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042247331-RENAME-command&#34;&gt;RENAME&lt;/a&gt; commands, especially on datasets with many variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated documentation to describe how to use new functionality when &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040060112-Organizing-Variables&#34;&gt;organizing variables&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360059213452-Category-Differences&#34;&gt;Category Differences&lt;/a&gt; article with new information for broad release.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new Crunch Automation commands to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360045984071-Recoding-case-level-missing-valid-values-rebasing-&#34;&gt;Recoding&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated and added new info to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044362492-The-Definitive-Guide-to-Importing-and-Preparing-Data&#34;&gt;Importing and Preparing data definitive guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more &amp;lsquo;import data&amp;rsquo; examples in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044732771-Working-with-Data-and-Datasets&#34;&gt;Working with Data and Datasets&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.18</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-21/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Added the ability for organizations to route user questions and problems directly to personnel or online resources (blogs, knowledge base, help center, videos, etc) for any folder via the &amp;ldquo;Report an Issue&amp;rdquo; menu option. For example, you may want to configure a top-level regional folder to route user issues to your own, branded https://help.mycomany.com and configure a lower-level folder to route user questions to a specific email address like usa-questions@mycompany.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability for organizations to route user questions and problems directly to personnel or online resources (blogs, knowledge base, help center, videos, etc) for any folder via the &amp;ldquo;Report an Issue&amp;rdquo; menu option. For example, you may want to configure a top-level regional folder to route user issues to your own, branded &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.mycomany.com&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;https://help.mycomany.com&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and configure a lower-level folder to route user questions to a specific email address like &lt;code&gt;usa-questions@mycompany.com&lt;/code&gt;. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360061158712-End-user-support-requests&#34;&gt;help article&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support that tracks how users are interacting with datasets: upon request, Crunch will send clickstream data to each organization&amp;rsquo;s Google Analytics reports. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360061144172-Understanding-end-user-usage&#34;&gt;help article&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the following improvements to the variable organizer when accessed by selecting &amp;ldquo;Edit Variables&amp;rdquo; from dataset properties:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dragging and dropping are smoother, and a dropzone now appears with a dashed border where the dragged variables are moved, making it easier to see.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When clicking or dragging to &amp;ldquo;Move&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; a &amp;lsquo;Move to&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo; dialog appears, which allows you to more easily navigate your folder hierarchy and even create new folders as part of the moving process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how &amp;ldquo;Export this table&amp;rdquo; performs so that it correctly exports the displayed measure and decimal place setting in multitable view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how the &amp;ldquo;Above table&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Below table&amp;rdquo; bases options are properly reflected in the tab book export for crosstabs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the &lt;code&gt;MINUS&lt;/code&gt; modifier info to the DISPLAY command. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038692-DISPLAY-command&#34;&gt;help article&lt;/a&gt; for more information and examples.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made speed improvements when working with large scripts or datasets in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038132-CHANGE-command&#34;&gt;CHANGE&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044079971-CREATE-MULTIPLE-SELECTION-command&#34;&gt;CREATE MULTIPLE SELECTION&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042457291-ORGANIZE-command&#34;&gt;ORGANIZE command&lt;/a&gt;s.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044080131-SET-DATES-command&#34;&gt;SET DATES command&lt;/a&gt; when working on derived variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038132-CHANGE-command&#34;&gt;CHANGE LABELS command&lt;/a&gt; to allow you to change subvariable labels for numeric arrays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to delete a script even if multitables or filters depend on any of the variables created by the script.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360061158712-End-user-support-requests&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; that describes how to use the &amp;ldquo;Report an Issue&amp;rdquo; feature within the Crunch web app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made improvements to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040059832-Target-Population&#34;&gt;Target Population&lt;/a&gt; help desk article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.17</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-14/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Improved the time marker bar so that when you click the diamond symbol it now expands to display the margin of error when confidence bands are enabled in time plots. Improved the export settings functionality (for both deck and tab book exports), so that it now features a &amp;lsquo;bases&amp;rsquo; options for numeric measures. Added performance improvements and fixed various bugs to the export settings crosstab sections (tab book and edit slide).</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the time marker bar so that when you click the diamond symbol it now expands to display the margin of error when confidence bands are enabled in time plots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the export settings functionality (for both deck and tab book exports), so that it now features a &amp;lsquo;bases&amp;rsquo; options for numeric measures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added performance improvements and fixed various bugs to the export settings crosstab sections (tab book and edit slide).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed how decks appear, which are now alphabetically sorted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how long format exports are handled when &amp;ldquo;All variables on one sheet&amp;rdquo; is selected so that legends are now separately included for both crosstabs and numeric exports where applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhanced how calculations are performed when population estimates in a crosstab include a categorical date variable – each wave is now assumed to represent the entire population.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the API email policy so that users with appropriate permissions may still change a user&amp;rsquo;s email through the &lt;code&gt;/api/user/&amp;lt;userID&amp;gt;/change_email/&lt;/code&gt; endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused some sCrunch library commands to fail when fetching data from the &lt;code&gt;/tables/&lt;/code&gt; endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in the Crunch Automation script runner that caused certain Unicode strings in categories to be incorrectly matched.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a new &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/categories/360006281331-Integrations&#34;&gt;section&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360061204751-Crunch-importers-overview&#34;&gt;overview&lt;/a&gt; article for integrations, in order to help users easily find information on how to import data from popular data-collection platforms into Crunch. We&amp;rsquo;ll be adding new information on all of the platforms in the coming weeks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new information about how to use web app and Crunch Automation for &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360045631232-Nets-on-a-multiple-response-variable&#34;&gt;nets on a multiple response variable&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.16</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-05-07/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Added the ability to show the title and description for a column variable beneath the graph in edit preview and dashboards. Improved how datasets on a dashboard appear on a landing page so that the member&amp;rsquo;s panel no longer switches to a dashboard when closing it. Fixed a bug that improves how formulas for subtotals and differences are saved. Made numerous improvements to the Confirmit importer, including:  Cleaned up the formatting of both folders, variable names, and descriptions.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to show the title and description for a column variable beneath the graph in edit preview and dashboards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how datasets on a dashboard appear on a landing page so that the member&amp;rsquo;s panel no longer switches to a dashboard when closing it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that improves how formulas for subtotals and differences are saved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made numerous improvements to the Confirmit importer, including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cleaned up the formatting of both folders, variable names, and descriptions. Some variables were being missed on import and are now being imported properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added proper support for numeric array integrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more language support in Confirmit integrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Re-enabled the hypothesis testing &amp;ldquo;set&amp;rdquo; comparison option when working with a categorical array that has subvariables within the columns and categories within the rows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how Crunch Automation handles scripts that have numerous commands (&amp;gt; than 1MB) or on a dataset with 1000s of variables. The validation step now returns a 202 asynchronous progress response.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;developer-documentation&#34;&gt;Developer documentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a new article about &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360060324892-Insertions&#34;&gt;Insertions&lt;/a&gt;. You can read more about definition attributes in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042410872-Variable-Definitions#toc11&#34;&gt;Variable Definitions&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.15</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-30/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Improved the web app by displaying a descriptive error when an integration update fails. Improved the user experience when deleting a deck. Moved the N label in graphs to the bottom right and increased the font size.  API Endpoints and API Reference  Updated the API so that you can now add a suffix to your &amp;ldquo;join&amp;rdquo; API call, which allows the source variables to include a suffix to avoid conflicts.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the web app by displaying a descriptive error when an integration update fails.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the user experience when deleting a deck.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moved the N label in graphs to the bottom right and increased the font size.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the API so that you can now add a suffix to your &amp;ldquo;join&amp;rdquo; API call, which allows the source variables to include a suffix to avoid conflicts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360054720992-The-Quick-Editor-a-generator-for-Crunch-Automation#toc3&#34;&gt;Variable Editor (v2.1.0)&lt;/a&gt; with the following improvements:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support for turning numeric variables into numeric arrays via the array builder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added checks to verify user-entered variable titles are unique.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed bug so that organizing variables into the hidden folder doesn&amp;rsquo;t create a new personal folder called hidden.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set reasonable default column widths on the variables tab and turned off automatic auto-fit resizing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed bug in automation script by adding backticks to variable aliases that contain spaces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reset and disabled the source variable folder, title, description, and notes fields when using the array builder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360060308211-Envelope-Specification&#34;&gt;Envelope Specification&lt;/a&gt; documentation to provide more information about Shoji, a JSON-based data interchange format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360060244212-Integrations-Continuous-updates-to-your-dataset-via-the-direct-importers&#34;&gt;Integrations: Continuous updates to your dataset via the direct importers&lt;/a&gt; documentation to show how to enable users to add new cases that have been directly imported, without having to go through an append process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.14</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-23/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Released the time plot feature to wide access, so that &amp;lsquo;time periods&amp;rsquo; with no data at the beginning or end of a time range are now omitted from the horizontal axis — this is now dynamic as you add or remove categories. See the announcement and help documentation for more information. Fixed a bug that prevented datasets that are shared with users from appearing in search results.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Released the time plot feature to wide access, so that &amp;lsquo;time periods&amp;rsquo; with no data at the beginning or end of a time range are now omitted from the horizontal axis — this is now dynamic as you add or remove categories. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/dev/features/new-time-plots/&#34;&gt;announcement&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057226852-Time-series-analysis-with-time-plots&#34;&gt;help documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that prevented datasets that are shared with users from appearing in search results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how N values display on a time plot after selecting a categorical date entry on a group filter (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where hypothesis testing colors were displayed incorrectly after showing/hiding rows in edit mode.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added ALTER ARRAY ADD EMPTY SUBVARIABLE command, which allows you to modify a non-derived array by adding new empty subvariables. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360059806532-ALTER-ARRAY-ADD-EMPTY-SUBVARIABLE-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360056799552-CREATE-MULTIPLE-DICHOTOMY-FROM-CONDITIONS-command&#34;&gt;CREATE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY FROM CONDITIONS command&lt;/a&gt; with improved instructions and use cases. It&amp;rsquo;s now possible to use a single expression to define the base either by indicating the &lt;code&gt;VALID&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;MISSING&lt;/code&gt; rows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more functions that can be used with Crunch Automation scripts (&lt;code&gt;KEEP_AFTER&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;KEEP_BEFORE&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;KEEP_BETWEEN&lt;/code&gt;). See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292#toc8&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.13</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-16/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed a bug on the Decipher importer to instead show a full list when importing. Fixed a bug so that dashboards appear properly when switching tabs. Fixed a bug so that dropdown menus for individual dashboard tiles work properly. Improved PowerPoint graph exports to correctly show expected colors for negative values. Enhanced how standard deviations appear in tab book exports so that they correctly show the row variable as a numeric measure.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h2 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug on the Decipher importer to instead show a full list when importing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug so that dashboards appear properly when switching tabs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug so that dropdown menus for individual dashboard tiles work properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved PowerPoint graph exports to correctly show expected colors for negative values.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhanced how standard deviations appear in tab book exports so that they correctly show the row variable as a numeric measure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how time plots reposition in the far-right location when the horizontal axis range changes (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that causes new connections to Qualtrics to fail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how the time marker for a time plot appears when it moves to the left of its docked position — it now retains that position when also selecting a filter, applying a weight, or enabling/disabling confidence bands (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved horizontal and vertical bar graphs so that negative values now display.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed dashboard URLs that specify filters to work properly when another filter is added.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made improvements about aliases and variables in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292-Crunch-Automation-basics&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation basics&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.12</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-09/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Refactored the dataset importer and integrations in order to provide a more consistent and streamlined user experience. Fixed an issue with the importer that caused integrations to fail to render when there are too many surveys. Fixed an issue with variable sources and importer not working properly for Decipher integrations. Made various tweaks to Permissions Management and Dataset Importer panel UI to cause progressively loaded lists to render more consistently.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactored the dataset importer and integrations in order to provide a more consistent and streamlined user experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with the importer that caused integrations to fail to render when there are too many surveys.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with variable sources and importer not working properly for Decipher integrations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made various tweaks to Permissions Management and Dataset Importer panel UI to cause progressively loaded lists to render more consistently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the design of the section headers in the Export Settings panels to improve usability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the category selector for a time plot so that users can now select empty categories to be displayed on the plot (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue in which switching tabs was not working properly for some dashboards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#get-/search/aggregate/&#34;&gt;search aggregation&lt;/a&gt; endpoint that caused an error when the user provides an empty query string.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an sCrunch bug that occurred when using Backfill functionality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new ADD CATEGORIES command, which allows you to add extra empty categories to categorical variables. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360059442431-ADD-CATEGORIES-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;back-endcrunchdb&#34;&gt;Back-end/CrunchDB&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved performance speed when accessing slides in a deck.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created new help desk article that describes the new &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360059213452-Category-Differences&#34;&gt;Category Differences&lt;/a&gt; feature (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.11</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-04-02/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Updated how descriptions are handled, which now allows them to extend to the entire width beneath a graph as needed. Changed the default to &amp;lsquo;aspect ratio&amp;rsquo; when rendering time plots in &amp;ldquo;Tables and graphs&amp;rdquo; mode (in early access). Improved search results by including:  whether or not a dataset is a view, and for variable results, the type is now included.   Fixed a bug so that now weighted numeric-array analyses are successful.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated how descriptions are handled, which now allows them to extend to the entire width beneath a graph as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changed the default to &amp;lsquo;aspect ratio&amp;rsquo; when rendering time plots in &amp;ldquo;Tables and graphs&amp;rdquo; mode (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved search results by including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;whether or not a dataset is a view, &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;for variable results, the type is now included.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug so that now weighted numeric-array analyses are successful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved how stacked vertical bar graphs appear by allocating additional space for vertical axis labels so that they fully display.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the time plot feature so that &amp;lsquo;time periods&amp;rsquo; with no data at the beginning or end of a time range are now omitted from the horizontal axis — this is now dynamic as you add or remove categories (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the new argument &lt;code&gt;dryrun&lt;/code&gt; to the Crunch Automation script endpoint, which prevents the script from executing and only performs validations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the new argument &lt;code&gt;ELSE INTO NULL&lt;/code&gt; to the CREATE CONVERT command, which allows you to indicate that any extra value should go to the No Data category. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360047136371-CREATE-CONVERT-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for an example.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360049913732-Example-files-for-Crunch-Automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation example scripts&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.10</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-26/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Added feature to show values on a time plot when the user has Display &amp;gt; Values selected in the extended panel of the Display Controller (in early access). Updated horizontal bar graphs so that labels on an axis are no longer truncated. Added hint text to alert users who have any profile analyses saved to a deck, since these analyses cannot be exported via the &amp;ldquo;Export from deck&amp;rdquo; panel.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added feature to show values on a time plot when the user has Display &amp;gt; Values selected in the extended panel of the Display Controller (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated horizontal bar graphs so that labels on an axis are no longer truncated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added hint text to alert users who have any profile analyses saved to a deck, since these analyses cannot be exported via the &amp;ldquo;Export from deck&amp;rdquo; panel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a &amp;ldquo;Fit to tile&amp;rdquo; option, which is available in the Edit panel for saved analyses that have the &amp;lsquo;time plot&amp;rsquo; visualization type (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changed several user-level permissions to enable better sharing and editing of datasets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that occurred when searching for personal variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the dataset scripts endpoint by including the script ID on the shoji tuple.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhanced the &lt;code&gt;POST /api/account/users/&lt;/code&gt; endpoint to enable granting users the ability to edit datasets separately from creating datasets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to perform backfill replacements without a filter in sCrunch (full column).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added Python 3.4 support to sCrunch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Released sCrunch version 0.9.3.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to use reference functions to act on a variable number of input variables for the &lt;code&gt;RENAME&lt;/code&gt; command. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042247331-RENAME-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved support for Unicode characters in Crunch Automation strings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added more descriptive information on how to use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044567952-CREATE-MULTIPLE-DICHOTOMY-WITH-RECODE-command&#34;&gt;CREATE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY WITH RECODE command&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292-Crunch-Automation-basics&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation basics&lt;/a&gt; article with better examples.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.9</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-19/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Reorganized the options on the Export settings panels for both slide exports and tab book exports for improved usability. Please refer to the help page for more information. Added a legend entry when exporting a single-measure numeric value to reflect what measure is being exported. Fixed the horizontal axis for time plots so that they no longer show empty time periods that might be present at either the beginning or the end of the categorical dates (in early access).</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reorganized the options on the Export settings panels for both slide exports and tab book exports for improved usability. Please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040498732-Exporting-Tab-Books#toc1&#34;&gt;help page&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a legend entry when exporting a single-measure numeric value to reflect what measure is being exported.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed the horizontal axis for time plots so that they no longer show empty time periods that might be present at either the beginning or the end of the categorical dates (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved aspect ratio handling for time plots depicted in Tables and Graphs mode (in early access).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added responsiveness to changes in the decimal places setting for graphs in which the column variable is a numeric value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enabled sCrunch datasets to run Crunch Automation commands, via &lt;code&gt;dataset.scripts.execute(&amp;lt;script body&amp;gt;)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;code&gt;EACH MISSING&lt;/code&gt; functionality to the OVERWRITE VALUES command. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057819011-OVERWRITE-VALUES-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the docs to include using an optional &lt;code&gt;,&lt;/code&gt; (comma) between statements for both the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042039192-CREATE-CATEGORICAL-CASE-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CATEGORICAL CASE&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360045656352-CREATE-NUMERIC-CASE-command&#34;&gt;CREATE NUMERIC CASE&lt;/a&gt; commands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042247331-RENAME-command&#34;&gt;RENAME command&lt;/a&gt; with improved syntax and examples (logical expressions in Crunch automation now support both &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; with datetime strings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;code&gt;STARTSWITH()&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;ENDSWITH()&lt;/code&gt; functionality. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292#toc7&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;developer-documentation&#34;&gt;Developer documentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a new function on automation expressions (&lt;code&gt;add_valid&lt;/code&gt;), which returns a numeric column with the sum of the input numeric variables; returns no data when all the columns are missing. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042411792#toc8&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cleaned up and organized the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040498012-Orientation-videos&#34;&gt;Orientation Videos&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new content and better examples to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360052195131-The-Definitive-Guide-to-Tracking&#34;&gt;Definitive Guide to Tracking&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cleaned up the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042695251-How-to-Use-the-Crunch-API&#34;&gt;How to Use the Crunch API&lt;/a&gt; article to help enable faster onboarding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.8</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed case where missing columns in the response data can fail when importing a Qualtrics dataset. Adjusted y-axis min value so that it now be set to zero for the case of time plots. Fixed the extended panel when it opens from the display controller so that it no longer shrinks the displayed table or graph. Corrected how axis and tooltip labeling appears when displaying population estimates along the vertical axis of a time plot.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed case where missing columns in the response data can fail when importing a Qualtrics dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjusted y-axis min value so that it now be set to zero for the case of time plots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed the extended panel when it opens from the display controller so that it no longer shrinks the displayed table or graph.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corrected how axis and tooltip labeling appears when displaying population estimates along the vertical axis of a time plot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added improved code sample to &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#get-/search/&#34;&gt;Cross-dataset search&lt;/a&gt; endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added improved code sample and a &lt;code&gt;200&lt;/code&gt; response example to &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#get-/search/aggregate/&#34;&gt;Aggregate search results by folder&lt;/a&gt; endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the function &lt;code&gt;makeDimTransform()&lt;/code&gt; to the &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt; package, which helps set transforms on slide analyses, such as color palettes, hiding elements, and setting the order.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Also added the ability to use &lt;code&gt;palettes()&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;defaultPalette()&lt;/code&gt; functions in the &lt;code&gt;R&lt;/code&gt; package to access the palettes associated with a dataset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;MISSING&lt;/code&gt; functionality added to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360056799552-CREATE-MULTIPLE-DICHOTOMY-FROM-CONDITIONS-command&#34;&gt;CREATE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY FROM CONDITIONS command&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;SELECTED&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;LABELS&lt;/code&gt; arguments added to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044079971-CREATE-MULTIPLE-SELECTION-command&#34;&gt;CREATE MULTIPLE SELECTION command&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a new help desk article for &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040054752-How-to-upload-a-PowerPoint-template&#34;&gt;How to upload a PowerPoint template&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.7</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-03-05/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed bug that prevented users from editing categories that are associated with an existing formula. Improved the ability to add scoring for Qualtrics variables in the Crunch app. Fixed bug that prevented you from exporting datasets in CSV format that explicitly included formulas as their variables. Fixed the ability to show categories more reliably at all screen sizes in the filter builder/categorical variable builder. Improved Confirmit integration to increase performance, fixed some bugs when multiple languages are in play, and reduced the dependency of the system on provided wsdl files.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed bug that prevented users from editing categories that are associated with an existing formula.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved the ability to add scoring for Qualtrics variables in the Crunch app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed bug that prevented you from exporting datasets in CSV format that explicitly included formulas as their variables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed the ability to show categories more reliably at all screen sizes in the filter builder/categorical variable builder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved Confirmit integration to increase performance, fixed some bugs when multiple languages are in play, and reduced the dependency of the system on provided &lt;code&gt;wsdl&lt;/code&gt; files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display controller is now properly displayed as window width is decreased.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed bug that led to unwanted slowness when processing formulas as part of the &lt;code&gt;/dataset/ID/table&lt;/code&gt; endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed bug on &lt;code&gt;/dataset/ID/table&lt;/code&gt; endpoint when one of the requested formulas is not applicable for any reason.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added OVERWRITE VALUES command, which allows you to alter specific cells in categorical and numeric variables without altering the type. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057819011-OVERWRITE-VALUES-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;code&gt;NULL&lt;/code&gt; functionality to the SET EXCLUSION command. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042038272-SET-EXCLUSION-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the DISPLAY command, which now allows you to add subtotals substracting other categories via the &lt;code&gt;MINUS&lt;/code&gt; modifier.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the CREATE ARRAY CASE command, which now allows you to create a new array without indicating a background variable. When using it this way, all the cells in the array that do not match any of the conditions will default to &lt;code&gt;No Data&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-website-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and website improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added documentation for &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057226852-Time-series-analysis-with-time-plots&#34;&gt;Time series analysis with time plots&lt;/a&gt;, which is currently available in Early Access mode.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.6</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-26/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Fixed a bug that occurred when dragging a numeric variable onto a time plot as the &amp;lsquo;Cell&amp;rsquo; mean variable. Fixed issues that occurred when using the &amp;lsquo;Manage user&amp;rsquo; invite and edit forms. Changed the behavior of how notifications appear when a deck is closed. Added the ability to drag and drop numeric array variables with all other variables types in the &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; view.  API Endpoints and API Reference  Qualtrics is now supported as an integration type.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that occurred when dragging a numeric variable onto a time plot as the &amp;lsquo;Cell&amp;rsquo; mean variable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed issues that occurred when using the &amp;lsquo;Manage user&amp;rsquo; invite and edit forms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Changed the behavior of how notifications appear when a deck is closed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to drag and drop numeric array variables with all other variables types in the &amp;lsquo;Tables &amp;amp; Graphs&amp;rsquo; view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualtrics is now supported as an integration type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Searches can now be filtered by folder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search Aggregation endpoint added to show aggregated counts of search results on a per-dataset basis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When users are created by sharing datasets, projects, or teams, the users are now created under the account associated with the dataset, project, or team. Previously users created this way had their users created under a new single-user account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the &lt;code&gt;subvariables_of&lt;/code&gt; function, which allows you to pass in multiple aliases of array functions. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292#subvariables_of&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;back-endcrunchdb&#34;&gt;Back-end/CrunchDB&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made performance improvements when running cube queries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-and-websites-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk and websites improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a link on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/&#34;&gt;Crunch website&lt;/a&gt; support menu to our development release notes where you can review all the latest product enhancements we have completed and subscribe to future release notes via email if you want to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made additional edits and updates to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292-Crunch-Automation-basics&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation basics&lt;/a&gt; help desk article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.5</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-19/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application  Added text input that allows you to write custom messages that are used when inviting users from the Members panel. Fixed an issue where stats don&amp;rsquo;t show up when using a filter builder on datasets where you do not have editing permissions. Made multiple response x 2 (MR x MR) analyses display correct N base value on graphs. Fixed a bug that occurred when inviting editors. Simplified options for dataset sharing.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added text input that allows you to write custom messages that are used when inviting users from the Members panel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where stats don&amp;rsquo;t show up when using a filter builder on datasets where you do not have editing permissions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made multiple response x 2 (MR x MR) analyses display correct N base value on graphs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that occurred when inviting editors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simplified options for dataset sharing. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/dev/features/dataset-sharing/&#34;&gt;announcement&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to set filters and weights when creating slides in &lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New commands&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added REPLACE CATEGORICAL ARRAY CASE, which allows you to replace values in an array in place without creating a new variable. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360056804932-REPLACE-CATEGORICAL-ARRAY-CASE-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added CREATE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY FROM CONDITIONS, which allows you to create a new multiple response variable indicating the logic of each column without having to create intermediate logical variables. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360056799552-CREATE-MULTIPLE-DICHOTOMY-FROM-CONDITIONS-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the CREATE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY WITH RECODE command, which now allows multiple categories on the &lt;code&gt;SELECTED&lt;/code&gt; option. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044567952-CREATE-MULTIPLE-DICHOTOMY-WITH-RECODE-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the CREATE MULTIPLE SELECTION command, which now allows you to specify aliases of the subvariables to be created. If not included, they will default to the alias of the new array suffixed with a positional number. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044079971-CREATE-MULTIPLE-SELECTION-command&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360056505351-Finding-your-starting-point&#34;&gt;quick start guide&lt;/a&gt; to better help new visitors find they&amp;rsquo;re starting point in Crunch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057170591-Dataset-Sharing-for-Dataset-Editors&#34;&gt;new article&lt;/a&gt; for dataset sharing for Dataset Editors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.4</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Changes
 Made the invite button available before the permission list is loaded. Added support for analyses involving a multiple response variable crossed with a numeric array variable.  Bugfixes
 Fixed timeplot, which was displaying wrong N count. Fixed tooltip value for Margin of Error. Fixed broken scrollbar behavior on filter builder in the categorical variable builder.  SDKs (rCrunch, pyCrunch, and sCrunch)  Improved sCrunch Backfill code.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch web application&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the invite button available before the permission list is loaded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added support for analyses involving a multiple response variable crossed with a numeric array variable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bugfixes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed timeplot, which was displaying wrong N count.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed tooltip value for Margin of Error.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed broken scrollbar behavior on filter builder in the categorical variable builder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved sCrunch Backfill code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Released the CREATE NUMERIC ARRAY command. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360057078531-CREATE-NUMERIC-ARRAY-command&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Published the following Qualtrics support documentation:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360056831391-How-to-import-from-Qualtrics-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;How to import from Qualtrics into Crunch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360056419652-How-your-survey-metadata-maps-from-Qualtrics-into-Crunch&#34;&gt;How your survey metadata maps from Qualtrics into Crunch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.3</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-02-05/</guid>
      <description>Crunch Web Application Bug fixes:
 Fixed broken pagination buttons on bar plots Fixed a bug that caused analysis titles and descriptions to display twice in dashboards view and edit tile panel. Made additional improvements to the categorical array builder, including the loading of saved expressions which include parentheses.  Other changes:
 Re-labeled column headers in Edit Categories panel. Hid &amp;ldquo;viztype&amp;rdquo; selector for numeric array analyses.  API Endpoints and API Reference  Improved search performance for folder-sorted search results.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h2 id=&#34;crunch-web-application&#34;&gt;Crunch Web Application&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bug fixes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed broken pagination buttons on bar plots&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that caused analysis titles and descriptions to display twice in dashboards view and edit tile panel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made additional improvements to the categorical array builder, including the loading of saved expressions which
include parentheses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other changes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Re-labeled column headers in Edit Categories panel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hid &amp;ldquo;viztype&amp;rdquo; selector for numeric array analyses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved search performance for folder-sorted search results. More speedups are on the way!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the way datasets that are associated with an integration to allow for new categories, subvariables, and
changes to the order of categories and subvariables.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added capability for sCrunch to back-fill data values via CSV file.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;website&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added Feature Announcements section, which is linked to from the search menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added the ability for end-users to subscribe to automatically receive feature announcements via email.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new &lt;code&gt;straightline&lt;/code&gt; function in automation for use in logical expressions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;product-documentation&#34;&gt;Product Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Published new article &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360054720992-The-Quick-Editor-a-generator-for-Crunch-Automation&#34;&gt;The Quick Editor: a generator for Crunch Automation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.2</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-29/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app  Refactor and performance enhancements to Search, making it easier for you to find things. Fix issue where dates could be shown incorrectly on project browser. We understand how frustrating it is when dates don&amp;rsquo;t appear correctly so we fixed this. Search behavior has now been changed to only search when you press return. Focusing on the control will open any previously obtained results. This will make search queries easier to use.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-app&#34;&gt;Crunch app&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refactor and performance enhancements to Search, making it easier for you to find things.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix issue where dates could be shown incorrectly on project browser. We understand how frustrating it is when dates don&amp;rsquo;t appear correctly so we fixed this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search behavior has now been changed to only search when you press return. Focusing on the control will open any previously obtained results. This will make search queries easier to use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix improper results and behavior when using Target Group Base in Profiles mode. We think the new ordering of results will delight you!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Numerous edits and fixes, including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a new endpoint (&lt;code&gt;/scripts/collapse&lt;/code&gt;). See &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#post-/datasets/-dataset_id-/scripts/collapse&#34;&gt;docs&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added new documentation for the &lt;code&gt;/datasets/all/&lt;/code&gt; endpoint. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/#get-/datasets/all/&#34;&gt;docs&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Numerous edits made to the non-endpoint reference docs, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/sections/360008315951-Start-Here&#34;&gt;Getting Started articles&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044735351-Working-with-Variables&#34;&gt;Working with Variables&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042410872-Variable-Definitions&#34;&gt;Variable Definitions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sdks-rcrunch-pycrunch-and-scrunch&#34;&gt;SDKs (&lt;code&gt;rCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;pyCrunch&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;sCrunch&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can now create numeric array variables in &lt;code&gt;deriveArray()&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;makeArray()&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;code&gt;REPLACE&lt;/code&gt; functionality to both the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042039192-CREATE-CATEGORICAL-CASE-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CATEGORICAL CASE&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360042039012-CREATE-CATEGORICAL-RECODE-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CATEGORICAL RECODE&lt;/a&gt; commands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360044362492-The-Definitive-Guide-to-Importing-and-Preparing-Data&#34;&gt;The Definitive Guide to Importing and Preparing Data&lt;/a&gt; article to include numerous new examples and uses cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Numerous additions to &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041769292-Crunch-Automation-basics&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation basics&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.1</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/release-notes/2021-01-22/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app  Provide you with the ability to customize table slide exports. See the help documentation for more information. Improve the &amp;lsquo;Margin of Error / Cell details&amp;rsquo; feature. See the help documentation for more information. Fix to the UI so that it now correctly shows the N range on a categorical array graph.  API Endpoints and API Reference  API endpoint documentation is live in its new home! See Crunch API Reference for more information.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-app&#34;&gt;Crunch app&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide you with the ability to customize table slide exports. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360041481052-Customizing-your-tables-for-export-or-dashboards&#34;&gt;help documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the &amp;lsquo;Margin of Error / Cell details&amp;rsquo; feature. See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360040932251-Customizing-a-Table-or-Graph#more-options&#34;&gt;help documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fix to the UI so that it now correctly shows the N range on a categorical array graph.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;api-endpoints-and-api-reference&#34;&gt;API Endpoints and API Reference&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;API endpoint documentation is live in its new home! See &lt;a href=&#34;https://crunch.io/api/reference/&#34;&gt;Crunch API Reference&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crunch-automation&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added three new commands: &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360053423591-CREATE-MULTIPLE-DICHOTOMY-EXTEND-command&#34;&gt;CREATE MULTIPLE DICHOTOMY EXTEND&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360053423671-CREATE-CATEGORICAL-ARRAY-CASE-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CATEGORICAL ARRAY CASE&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/articles/360054595731-CREATE-CATEGORICAL-SCALE-command&#34;&gt;CREATE CATEGORICAL SCALE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nearly every &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/sections/360010677071-Crunch-Automation-commands&#34;&gt;Crunch Automation article&lt;/a&gt; now has new content, use cases, and example scripts. Check them out if you haven&amp;rsquo;t visited them in awhile!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;help-desk-improvements&#34;&gt;Help desk improvements&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Numerous CSS fixes to improve the look, feel, and navigation of our &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.crunch.io/hc/en-us/&#34;&gt;help center&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content:encoded>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
