<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>feature on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/categories/feature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in feature on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 11:52:22 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/categories/feature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>See the margin of error and other helpful statistics in tables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 11:52:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</guid>
      <description>By using the new options panel revealed by clicking the three-dots icon in the display controller, users can choose which of these figures to display in the tooltip for table cells. The default statistics shown are the margin of error and unweighted base. Your chosen cell details are persisted as a user preference. For margin of error, you can also specify the number of decimal places you want to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greater flexibility to customize exports of tables from decks and dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-export-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 15:00:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-export-settings/</guid>
      <description>Back in September, we added a variety of advanced calculations to include in tab books (exported multitables) and other options to customize the exported tables. We&amp;rsquo;ve now added these same customization options to tables saved to (and exported from) the deck.
This can be helpful if you need to:
  Show more than one measure (percentages, counts, indices, Z-scores, population estimates) at once, or
  Have additional elements or measures included in your exports, such as pairwise comparison letters (ABCD), standard deviations, standard errors, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perform trend analysis on wave data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In time series analysis, we want to be able to identify trends. As we collect data, random fluctuations can obfuscate a trend. Smoothing is an analytic process whereby we ‘iron out’ differences between time periods by taking the average of previous periods. This is also known as a moving average. You can now apply smoothing to your analyses with just a few clicks. In the smoothing tab accessed by clicking ⋮ select ‘One-sided moving average’ and choose the number of periods to ‘look back’ at each point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greater flexibility to customize tab books</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 16:12:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</guid>
      <description>You can now choose a variety of advanced calculations to include in tab books (exported multitables) and other options to customize the exported tables. Table cells can now contain estimates of standard deviation and standard error, and column summaries can include the median of numeric values as well as the standard deviation for the column and standard error of the mean. Pairwise column significance tests can be conducted at the standard 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export whole dashboards or only the tabs you want, with the new selective tab exports feature for dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 09:39:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</guid>
      <description>Exporting from dashboards just got more flexible. Instead of always having to export the whole dashboard, users are now able to choose between exporting the whole dashboard (still the default), exporting the currently viewed tab, or choosing a custom selection of one or more tabs to export.
The new, simplified “Export…” option opens the new Export panel which gives the choice of PowerPoint or Excel formats, but for dashboards with tabs, it also now contains a “Tabs” control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combine categories in dashboard filter variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</guid>
      <description>The Groups on dashboards can now optionally allow multiple category selections to effectively combine categories in the filter. Dashboard editors can set an option on the configuration screen for dashboard “Groups” that allows users to make multiple selections within each variable. For example, if you choose an age categories variable as a group and turn on this new option, the dashboard users will be able to select both “18–24” and “25–34” simultaneously, thereby creating a filter that includes anyone aged 18–34.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customize your tables for export or dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 09:26:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve already been able to customize saved graphs, but now you can make those same edits to the rows and columns of saved tables, either for export or for display in dashboards. More specifically, you can now&amp;hellip;
 Hide any rows and/or columns of a table, including calculated rows/columns such as subtotals, leaving only those you want your export/dashboard consumers to see. Simply uncheck the box next to the row/column to hide it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easily create and recombine categorical arrays and multiple response variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-multiple-response-cat-array-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 17:34:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-multiple-response-cat-array-builder/</guid>
      <description>Array variables allow you to analyze together a set of variables that share a common structure and theme. For example, surveys often ask respondents to use a common scale to rate or respond to different prompts, sometimes in a grid, all sharing a common set of response categories. When analyzing the data, a categorical array variable lets users see all the items together. This structure allows users to easily compare lists of brands against a common set of attributes, or compare a set of statements against a common agreement scale — something that is much harder to do with distinct categorical variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use custom color palettes for your saved analyses</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 12:14:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been possible for some time to set custom colors for saved analyses in Crunch, but it&amp;rsquo;s been necessary to do this on a one-by-one basis which can be laborious and open to inconsistency. We now offer the ability to create custom color palettes, defined at the organization level, at folder levels, or both, which apply your chosen colors to newly created analyses as well as offering alternatives (e.g. for scales) that can be applied easily, as needed for particular analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect your PowerPoint decks with many new edit controls</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:11:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</guid>
      <description>When you create an analysis, you may need to edit it further for a PowerPoint export: for example, perhaps you want to hide &amp;lsquo;Not sure&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Prefer not to answer&amp;rsquo; categories, rename long labels, re-order the categories, give the whole analysis a descriptive title, or even simply change the coloring. You can now make these adjustments and more, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find all of those changes reflected in your PowerPoint and Excel exports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show value labels on graphs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</guid>
      <description>Users can now decide whether to show value labels for graphs and charts, both in Tables &amp;amp; Graphs mode and on dashboards. Value labels are these small numbers on graphs that show you the value represented by that bar/column/segment&amp;hellip;
 With the new feature turned on, these value labels will be displayed on all graphs you create. With the feature turned off (the default), the user needs to hover over a chart element to see a tool-tip with this value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding KPI tiles to dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-kpi-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:03:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-kpi-tile/</guid>
      <description>Dashboards can now contain KPI analyses that take a single value from a table and present it in a tile. Great for when there&amp;rsquo;s a key metric you want to highlight or track.
 Dataset editors can now add KPI analyses like these to dashboards. This allows you to show a key company metric – e.g. Brand Awareness – as a prominent value that grabs attention.
To create one, simply save an analysis of any kind – table, chart or variable card – that contains the value you want to show as a KPI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the interaction of two variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</guid>
      <description>To look in detail at your data, you sometimes need to create a variable that is the interaction of other categorical variables. You want to know not just how results differ between age groups or education level, but by age × education. The Crunch application lets you do this in just a few clicks by selecting the variables to interact — give the result a name (or accept the default of ‘x by y’) and you’re set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard tabs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</guid>
      <description>Dashboard tiles can now be placed across multiple tabs, making it easier to navigate large dashboards. As an editor, you are now able to:
  Create new tabs (as many as you&amp;rsquo;d like)
  Move tiles from one tab to another
  Give tabs meaningful names to aid navigation
  Delete tabs, choosing whether to delete any tiles or move them to another tab
  See our support documentation to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch&#39;s updated Member panels make it easy to see who has access to a dataset or folder</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-permissions-september-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 15:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-permissions-september-2019/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve made it much easier to view and change which of your users have access to your datasets and folders. If you are an editor on a dataset or folder, click the dataset or folder name in the header and select Members to open the permissions panel:
 When viewing dataset members, this panel will show all users who have access to this dataset and what type of access they have, regardless of how that access was granted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding rich-text tiles to dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 13:07:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can now add rich-text tiles to a dashboard. This can be used for dashboard analysis, terms and conditions, privacy notices, fieldwork dates and anything else the editor may wish to display. As an editor you are now able to:
  Compose text content to display as tiles using a WYSIWYG editor - no coding skills required.
  See a real-time preview of how your tile is going to look as you type and make formatting changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtering dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 10:16:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can add one or more variables to be used as filters across an entire dashboard with a simple drag-and-drop interface. This allows all dashboard viewers to get more out of your dashboards by customizing their view of the data. For example:
  Add demographic variables such as gender, age, education level, region, and ethnicity to allow your viewers to drill down on the customer populations that interest them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click to set the comparison column for hypothesis tests</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/click-to-compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/click-to-compare/</guid>
      <description>Tables in the application now let you set a column as the basis of comparison, shading the table to show which other columns are higher or lower than the reference column, and to what level of statistical significance. The test is a two-tailed t test comparing each column proportion in turn to the proportion in the reference column. In a multitable, the test is conducted between categories within each column variable, and not across column variables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizable dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 09:56:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</guid>
      <description>What are Crunch dashboards? A dashboard is a special view of your data that has been prepared with pre-made analyses — tables and graphs — designed to highlight key points for instant insight. Dashboards are great for conveying key information, drawn from your data, for users who don’t have the time (or the inclination) to do their own analysis. Crunch dashboards allow you to combine your important findings into a single display, perfect for sharing with colleagues and other end users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New hypothesis testing features in Crunch</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-hypothesis-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-hypothesis-tests/</guid>
      <description>Crunch tab book exports now include a new hypothesis testing option that computes all possible comparisons between columns of a two-way table. When users select the &amp;ldquo;Column t-test&amp;rdquo; option in the “Export tab book… &amp;gt; Customize” panel, columns in output will be lettered and differences that are significant at the .05 significance level are indicated by letters underneath the cell with the higher percentage. See here for details.
 An example of the exported result is shown below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Multitable Export</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-this-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-this-table/</guid>
      <description>Export all on a single page  Multitables are a great way to quickly find key relationships in your data. When exporting multitables, you now have three choices, allowing you to create just the right export for your needs.
 Export this table – instantly grab an XLSX file of just what you see on screen, using whatever display settings you have currently selected. Export this table (saved settings) – instantly grab an XLSX file of the table that you see on screen but with whatever settings you’ve chosen in the Export tab book &amp;gt; Customize panel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Organization of Datasets</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</guid>
      <description>Dataset folders allow you to organize your data hierarchically, similar to a file system as you might see in Windows Explorer or MacOS Finder. Folders make finding, organizing, and sharing data more intuitive.
  Folders can be used to organize large collections of datasets into more manageable units. If your organization imports data from many sources or has a large archive of previously imported data, you can organize them by source, time of import/survey, subject, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Deck Exports</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 10:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</guid>
      <description>We know that for many, PowerPoint slides remain central to delivering results and to paraphrase Mark Twain, &amp;ldquo;reports of PowerPoint&amp;rsquo;s death have been greatly exagerated&amp;rdquo;. Crunch has long offered exports of analyses and tab books to Excel files, which, in addition to their own value, enabled people to get results from Crunch to PowerPoint by copying a cell range from Excel into a slide. That’s a bit tedious, though, and we wanted to do better, which is why we are excited to announce that PowerPoint exports from Crunch are now available if you have ‘Early access’ enabled in the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subtotals for Categorical Data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 13:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch, we are constantly searching for ways to help our customers&amp;mdash;and their clients&amp;mdash;gain insights from their data. A common task in the market-research world is to take data that is essentially a scale&amp;mdash;rate from 1 to 10, or an ordinal range of responses from &amp;ldquo;Strongly agree&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Strongly disagree&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;and collapse it into a smaller number of bins. For example, if you asked people to rate their preference on a scale of 1-10 you might want to see how the people who provide a rating between 1 and 5 compare to those who rated it between 6 and 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is designed to make data accessible to many different audiences that have varying needs, expectations, and technical abilities. Our browse and analyze views allow data owners and analysts to quickly explore and analyze interesting insights in potentially large, complex datasets. However, not everyone has time to explore a dataset&amp;mdash;some need to see key findings at a glance.
To meet this executive-type need, we&amp;rsquo;re introducing a new dashboard feature.
 This dashboard provides a quick view of up to four analyses, right when you open a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crunch R Package 1.18.0 Released</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/r-package-1-18-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 18:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/r-package-1-18-0/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just released version 1.18.0 of the Crunch R package. Current package users should see a message when they load the package instructing you how to update to the latest version. New users (or anyone) can install this latest release from CRAN with
install.packages(&amp;quot;crunch&amp;quot;)  See the package website for further instructions.
Since the last CRAN release in June (1.17.0), some significant features have been added. A full list of changes can be found here, but here is an overview of the main additions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sentiment-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sentiment-analysis/</guid>
      <description>A wealth of information can be locked in text data. Our new “sentiment analysis” feature enables you to quantify and analyze just a bit of it: whether the text in question is on balance Positive, Neutral, or Negative — and then crosstab the derived sentiment variable just like any other variable to understand the variations among other groups in the dataset.
In the properties panel for text variables, you’ll notice the Classify button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refine your searches on Crunch</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/search-filters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 12:59:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/search-filters/</guid>
      <description>Search has been a part of Crunch from the beginning. In a system designed to house and share large volumes of data, the ability to quickly find the data that&amp;rsquo;s important right now is critical. We&amp;rsquo;re continually working to improve how data is indexed to make searching faster and more accurate, and we just added a couple new ways for you to refine your searches to get to what you are looking for faster and more easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>:bar_chart: New Header, New Font, New Graphs :chart_with_upwards_trend: </title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/visual-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 11:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/visual-updates/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been working on updating and improving the look of Crunch, and we wanted to take moment to call out a few of the recent improvements.
Let’s start at the top You may have noticed that we recently updated the Crunch header.
 This new top bar provides a more unified look throughout the application, and allows us to move user settings, dataset settings, and project settings into unobtrusive and consistently located dropdown menus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deliver New Data When You’re Ready</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/draft-and-publish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/draft-and-publish/</guid>
      <description>Lately we’ve been focusing on ways to make it easier for data owners to manage data for their clients. After all, Crunch isn’t just for analyzing data, it’s a tool for making everything about delivering data to clients faster, smoother, and more powerful.
To that end, we’ve recently developed a draft and publish feature that allows data owners to make significant changes to data accessible to their clients with minimal interruption to how those clients interact with the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tab Book Improvements</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/tab-book-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/tab-book-improvements/</guid>
      <description>We first released the tab book feature a while back, and since then, we’ve collected a number of great suggestions for how to enrich the feature. Tab books produce a static set of tables out of many variables and put results in an Excel sheet, for offline use when you don’t need interactive features like new filters or different weights. Our recent release includes several of those enhancements, most of which are new options available to you in the “export tab book” panel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
