<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analytics on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analytics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analytics on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 08:20:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Great new visualizations for time-series analyses and trackers</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-time-plots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 08:20:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-time-plots/</guid>
      <description>Line graphs are great at showing how values are changing over time and therefore ideal for tracking studies. Crunch&amp;rsquo;s line graphs have been completely redesigned to offer some great new features as well as improved usability and flexibility.
Category selection
Line graphs become really hard to read when there are lots of lines shown simultaneously, so Crunch now defaults to showing just the top 5, but you can pick whichever combination of lines (including showing more or fewer than 5) from the new &amp;ldquo;Select categories&amp;rdquo; interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See the margin of error and other helpful statistics in tables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/margin-of-error/</guid>
      <description>By using the new options panel revealed by clicking the three-dots icon in the display controller, users can choose which of these figures to display in the tooltip for table cells. The default statistics shown are the margin of error and unweighted base. Your chosen cell details are persisted as a user preference. For margin of error, you can also specify the number of decimal places you want to see.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
