<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Crunch</title>
    <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Crunch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All of your data in one place</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/first/</guid>
      <description>Your datasets are stored in the cloud, instantly available from anywhere. Find answers from any of your datasets using a powerful search tool. And you never have to worry about losing old data—it’s always there. Our innovative data version-control system allows you to undo changes and view earlier revisions, so you never have to worry about accidentally trashing your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complex analysis made easy</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/second/</guid>
      <description>An intuitive, visual interface allows anyone to browse—and to dig deeper. Drag and drop to create tables and charts; slice and filter further with a few clicks. All of this happens at the speed of thought, thanks to our purpose-built columnar database. Get instant results for most any query without any advance setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimized for survey research</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/third/</guid>
      <description>We’re survey experts. Crunch has special features to make survey analysis simple. We natively support data types like multiple response and &amp;ldquo;grid&amp;rdquo; questions. You can generate population weights and apply them automatically to all calculations. And you can code open-text data, including sentiment analysis, at the push of a button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborate better</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/fourth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/fourth/</guid>
      <description>Harness the power of a cloud platform to help people work together. Share your data with permission controls—no more emailing files. Use R and Python for scripting and modeling on the same data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish your findings</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/fifth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/fifth/</guid>
      <description>The CrunchBox lets you make your results available to the public. Embed a CrunchBox of your data in a blog post, press release, or dashboard. Viewers can filter and analyze the data right in the public report or article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlimited possibilities</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/sixth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/post/sixth/</guid>
      <description>Our APIs and client libraries make it easy to connect any data source and plug into your current workflow. Create custom integrations to import data from wherever. Perform complex modeling in R with no special code required. Plus, the ability to build custom visualizations in the web app are limitless. Our built-in support for R/Shiny apps allows you to design the perfect dashboard, and with our JavaScript SDK, you can create custom widgets and data portals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>