<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Case Studies on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Case Studies on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:25:37 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Universities</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/universities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:25:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/universities/</guid>
      <description>A collaboration between professors from three universities set out to deliver a series of reports entitled, “The State of the Nation: A 50-State COVID-19 Survey”. Survey data was collected from over 20,000 individuals, who responded to questions about reopening, mitigation, health guidelines, and more, with the survey running every two weeks.&#xA;The Director of Polling at one of the universities involved with the project reached out to Crunch.io for an easy-to-use survey tool that could integrate data from multiple sources, including national and state databases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaming</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:54:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gaming/</guid>
      <description>A video game company uses survey data from players to showcase audience insights and sell sponsorships to its advertisers. They chose Crunch.io because of the increased efficiency and time saved analyzing data with the drag-and-drop platform. They work with Crunch.io to analyze tracker data across multiple countries.&#xA;In preparation for a partner event, the company analysts built and presented interactive dashboards customized for each of their partners with Crunch.io’s no-coding, drag-and-drop dashboard builder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gojek</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gojek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:47:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gojek/</guid>
      <description>Gojek is the leading on-demand multi-service app platform and digital payment technology group in Southeast Asia. The company uses a call center to connect consumers to courier delivery and ride-hailing services. As of mid-2019, Gojek was a “Decacorn” valued at over $10 billion dollars with over 3,000 employees.&#xA;Gojek values Crunch.io for its ability to handle large-scale surveys. The company analyzes multiple tracker waves of data across a dozen countries and several customer satisfaction surveys across their rewards programs and multiple product lines in Crunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entertainment</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/entertainment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:45:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/entertainment/</guid>
      <description>When COVID-19 hit, a leading live entertainment and ticketing company didn’t panic. Instead, they launched a large gen-pop survey of almost 10,000 people across 8 countries to research how the pandemic is affecting their customers’ willingness to go to live events in the future.&#xA;The insights team analyzed key results within 48 hours of field completion with Crunch’s easy-to-use online platform. They prepared, analyzed data, built dashboards and delivered PowerPoint slides all within a few days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prodege</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/prodege/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 12:41:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/prodege/</guid>
      <description>Prodege is a leading provider of data and insights fueled by their global proprietary panel of 120 million members in over 125 countries. They leverage their innovative Prodege On-Demand platform (POD) to create and launch surveys for over 1,000 clients worldwide and chose to integrate Crunch.io within the POD platform so that their clients have access to data in exportable charts as well as online dashboards.&#xA;Prodege specializes in delivering fast, whether clients leverage Prodege’s managed services team of research experts or utilize their DIY version of POD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Council on Global Affairs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/chicago-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 11:22:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/chicago-council/</guid>
      <description>The Chicago Council on Global Affairs is an independent, nonpartisan organization that provides insight into global issues and policy.&#xA;The Chicago Council Survey team, part of the Lester Crown Center on US Foreign Policy, uses Crunch.io to analyze data from its annual survey on American public opinion and US foreign policy.&#xA;They have appended over 45 years of public opinion datasets into one dataset, previously only available in separate files, to enable simple and intuitive analysis of historical data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouGov</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/yougov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 18:39:31 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/yougov/</guid>
      <description>YouGov, whose current brand slogan is “the best panel - the best data - the best tools”, has one of the world’s largest research networks with a proprietary panel of over 17 million individuals in 50 markets. Researchers at YouGov use Crunch.io to perform analysis and deliver data and insights to clients via the Crunch.io web application, CrunchBoxes, and dashboards.&#xA;YouGov uses Crunch.io enterprise-wide for both custom research and Data Products, such as YouGov Profiles, which provides syndicated segmentation and product data for agencies and brands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
