<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Case Studies on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Case Studies on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 18:39:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gojek</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gojek/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 19:36:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/gojek/</guid>
      <description>Gojek is the leading on-demand multi-service app platform and digital payment technology group in Southeast Asia. The company uses a call center to connect consumers to courier delivery and ride-hailing services. Gojek is currently valued at $11 billion dollars with over 3,000 employees. Gojek works with multiple market research companies to conduct their own surveys. The company values Crunch.io’s ease of use for large scale surveys. Gojek uses Crunch.io to analyze multiple tracker waves of data across X countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metrixlab</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/metrixlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 19:36:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/metrixlab/</guid>
      <description>MetrixLab is a global research agency active in over 90 countries with half of the world’s top 100 brands as its clients. With Crunch.io, MetrixLab enables its clients to explore and engage with the data and survey results in real-time.
One of MetrixLab’s clients - a well-recognized, global fast-food franchise - used Crunch.io while conducting a taste test survey. Analysts were able to gather insights in real-time, segment individuals for additional questions based on immediate analysis of survey responses, and form additional focus groups to gain further insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activision Blizzard</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/activision-blizzard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 19:36:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/activision-blizzard/</guid>
      <description>Activision Blizzard uses survey data from players to showcase audience insights and sell sponsorships. Activision Blizzard chose Crunch.io because of the increased efficiency and time saved analyzing with the drag-and-drop platform. Activision Blizzard works with Crunch.io to analyze tracker data across multiple countries.
In preparation for a partner summit, Activision Blizzard built and presented interactive dashboards customized for each of their partners with Crunch.io’s no-coding, drag-and-drop dashboard builder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouGov</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/yougov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 18:39:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/case-studies/yougov/</guid>
      <description>YouGov has one of the world’s largest research networks with a proprietary panel of over 8 million individuals in 42 markets. YouGov is a power user of Crunch.io and uses Crunch.io to support its mission of “the best data - the best tools”. YouGov benefits from Crunch.io’s high-speed processing along with drag-and-drop ease of use.
Crunch.io currently hosts the YouGov Profiles data product, which provides syndicated segmentation and product data for agencies and brands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>