<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analyses on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analyses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analyses on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:18:29 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analyses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Perform trend analysis on wave data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In time series analysis, we want to be able to identify trends. As we collect data, random fluctuations can obfuscate a trend. Smoothing is an analytic process whereby we ‘iron out’ differences between time periods by taking the average of previous periods. This is also known as a moving average. You can now apply smoothing to your analyses with just a few clicks. In the smoothing tab accessed by clicking ⋮ select ‘One-sided moving average’ and choose the number of periods to ‘look back’ at each point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect your PowerPoint decks with many new edit controls</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:11:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</guid>
      <description>When you create an analysis, you may need to edit it further for a PowerPoint export: for example, perhaps you want to hide &amp;lsquo;Not sure&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Prefer not to answer&amp;rsquo; categories, rename long labels, re-order the categories, give the whole analysis a descriptive title, or even simply change the coloring. You can now make these adjustments and more, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find all of those changes reflected in your PowerPoint and Excel exports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show value labels on graphs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</guid>
      <description>Users can now decide whether to show value labels for graphs and charts, both in Tables &amp;amp; Graphs mode and on dashboards. Value labels are these small numbers on graphs that show you the value represented by that bar/column/segment&amp;hellip;
 With the new feature turned on, these value labels will be displayed on all graphs you create. With the feature turned off (the default), the user needs to hover over a chart element to see a tool-tip with this value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the interaction of two variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</guid>
      <description>To look in detail at your data, you sometimes need to create a variable that is the interaction of other categorical variables. You want to know not just how results differ between age groups or education level, but by age × education. The Crunch application lets you do this in just a few clicks by selecting the variables to interact — give the result a name (or accept the default of ‘x by y’) and you’re set.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
