<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analyses on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analyses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analyses on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:52:04 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/analyses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crunch&#39;s new visualizations for time-series analyses and trackers are now extended to Date/Time variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/date-time-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:52:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/date-time-variables/</guid>
      <description>Back in April this year, we announced that a great new visualization was available for time series analyses that used the new &amp;ldquo;Categorical Date&amp;rdquo; variable type. Existing time plots that used the older Date/Time variable type were unaffected and continued to use the previous line graph component. Since then, we&amp;rsquo;ve worked to extend the new line graph functionality to those original Date/Time variables so that everyone can benefit from their better design and functionality, and we can now announce that all time plots will be using the new visualization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sort your graph categories automatically</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sort-by-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 11:27:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sort-by-value/</guid>
      <description>You’ve been able to sort categories in tables in Crunch for a long time, but previously when you switched to a graph, that sorting was lost and the graph would show the categories in their original variable order. Now, the sorting you apply in a table will be carried through into a graph when you switch visualization type, as well as being made part of the analysis definition when you save a graph to the deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add subtotals to multiple response variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals-mr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 11:29:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals-mr/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors have been able to add subtotals (a.k.a. “nets”) to categorical and categorical array variables for a long time, but this hasn’t been the case for multiple response variables. There are many applications for subtotals on multiple response variables — a common one is a group of products or sub-brands within a brand, or a grouping of statements into themes. Previously, users had to define new variables with often complex logic to describe each combination, and then hide the input variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show calculated differences between categories</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotal-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 13:27:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotal-differences/</guid>
      <description>You’ve been able to create subtotals in Crunch for a long time, and they’re great for quickly seeing what proportion of respondents hold similar views, such as any level of agreement with a statement or any level of liking of a brand etc. But sometimes you also need to take into account the strength of opposing views — those who disagree or those who dislike, and for that you want to sum those who agree and take away the sum of those who disagree, leaving you with an overall measure you can use for simple comparisons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perform trend analysis on wave data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In time series analysis, we want to be able to identify trends. As we collect data, random fluctuations can obfuscate a trend. Smoothing is an analytic process whereby we ‘iron out’ differences between time periods by taking the average of previous periods. This is also known as a moving average. You can now apply smoothing to your analyses with just a few clicks. In the smoothing tab accessed by clicking ⋮ select ‘One-sided moving average’ and choose the number of periods to ‘look back’ at each point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export dashboards or the tabs you want, with the new selective tab exports feature</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 09:39:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</guid>
      <description>Exporting from dashboards just got more flexible. Instead of always having to export the whole dashboard, users are now able to choose between exporting the whole dashboard (still the default), exporting the currently viewed tab, or choosing a custom selection of one or more tabs to export.
The new, simplified “Export…” option opens the new Export panel which gives the choice of PowerPoint or Excel formats, but for dashboards with tabs, it also now contains a “Tabs” control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combine categories in dashboard filter variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</guid>
      <description>The Groups on dashboards can now optionally allow multiple category selections to effectively combine categories in the filter. Dashboard editors can set an option on the configuration screen for dashboard “Groups” that allows users to make multiple selections within each variable. For example, if you choose an age categories variable as a group and turn on this new option, the dashboard users will be able to select both “18–24” and “25–34” simultaneously, thereby creating a filter that includes anyone aged 18–34.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customize your tables for export or dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 09:26:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve already been able to customize saved graphs, but now you can make those same edits to the rows and columns of saved tables, either for export or for display in dashboards. More specifically, you can now&amp;hellip;
 Hide any rows and/or columns of a table, including calculated rows/columns such as subtotals, leaving only those you want your export/dashboard consumers to see. Simply uncheck the box next to the row/column to hide it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect your PowerPoint decks with many new edit controls</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:11:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</guid>
      <description>When you create an analysis, you may need to edit it further for a PowerPoint export: for example, perhaps you want to hide &amp;lsquo;Not sure&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Prefer not to answer&amp;rsquo; categories, rename long labels, re-order the categories, give the whole analysis a descriptive title, or even simply change the coloring. You can now make these adjustments and more, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find all of those changes reflected in your PowerPoint and Excel exports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show value labels on graphs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</guid>
      <description>Users can now decide whether to show value labels for graphs and charts, both in Tables &amp;amp; Graphs mode and on dashboards. Value labels are these small numbers on graphs that show you the value represented by that bar/column/segment&amp;hellip;
 With the new feature turned on, these value labels will be displayed on all graphs you create. With the feature turned off (the default), the user needs to hover over a chart element to see a tool-tip with this value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create the interaction of two variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/interaction-builder/</guid>
      <description>To look in detail at your data, you sometimes need to create a variable that is the interaction of other categorical variables. You want to know not just how results differ between age groups or education level, but by age × education. The Crunch application lets you do this in just a few clicks by selecting the variables to interact — give the result a name (or accept the default of ‘x by y’) and you’re set.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
