<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our mission</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/our-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 15:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/our-mission/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to empower marketers and market researchers to collaborate in a secure, cloud-based environment with a simple drag-and-drop interface to analyze, visualize, and deliver survey data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who we are</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 15:47:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>We’re a group of survey experts, market researchers, data scientists, and engineers.
We were frustrated by the current tools used to analyze, visualize, and deliver survey data. So, we built Crunch to bring simplicity and usability to survey data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy and Cookies Notice</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 17:09:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/about/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: May 31st, 2020 Protecting your privacy is very important to us at Crunch Cloud Analytics LLC (“Crunch”, “We”, “Us”, or “Our”), and we use our privacy and cookies notice to explain our practices regarding our collection and use of information that we receive through the online analytic services provided at www.crunch.io, and other related websites designated by Crunch (“Services”). This privacy and cookies notice applies to only those websites, services and applications included within our Services where this privacy notice is posted, and does not apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
