<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release Notes on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.5</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-19/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Added text input that allows you to write custom messages that are used when inviting users from the Members panel. Fixed an issue where stats don&amp;rsquo;t show up when using a filter builder on datasets where you do not have editing permissions. Made multiple response x 2 (MR x MR) analyses display correct N base value on graphs. Fixed a bug that occurred when inviting editors. Simplified options for dataset sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.4</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-12/</guid>
      <description>Crunch web application Changes
Made the invite button available before the permission list is loaded. Added support for analyses involving a multiple response variable crossed with a numeric array variable. Bugfixes
Fixed timeplot, which was displaying wrong N count. Fixed tooltip value for Margin of Error. Fixed broken scrollbar behavior on filter builder in the categorical variable builder. SDKs (rCrunch, pyCrunch, and sCrunch) Improved sCrunch Backfill code. Crunch Automation Released the CREATE NUMERIC ARRAY command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.3</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-02-05/</guid>
      <description>Crunch Web Application Bug fixes:
Fixed broken pagination buttons on bar plots Fixed a bug that caused analysis titles and descriptions to display twice in dashboards view and edit tile panel. Made additional improvements to the categorical array builder, including the loading of saved expressions which include parentheses. Other changes:
Re-labeled column headers in Edit Categories panel. Hid &amp;ldquo;viztype&amp;rdquo; selector for numeric array analyses. API Endpoints and API Reference Improved search performance for folder-sorted search results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.2</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-29/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app Refactor and performance enhancements to Search, making it easier for you to find things. Fix issue where dates could be shown incorrectly on project browser. We understand how frustrating it is when dates don&amp;rsquo;t appear correctly so we fixed this. Search behavior has now been changed to only search when you press return. Focusing on the control will open any previously obtained results. This will make search queries easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 2021.1</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/request-demo/release-notes/2021-01-22/</guid>
      <description>Crunch app Provide you with the ability to customize table slide exports. See the help documentation for more information. Improve the &amp;lsquo;Margin of Error / Cell details&amp;rsquo; feature. See the help documentation for more information. Fix to the UI so that it now correctly shows the N range on a categorical array graph. API Endpoints and API Reference API endpoint documentation is live in its new home! See Crunch API Reference for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
