<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tab books on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/tab-books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tab books on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 16:12:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/tab-books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Greater flexibility to customize tab books</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 16:12:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/customize-tab-book-exports/</guid>
      <description>You can now choose a variety of advanced calculations to include in tab books (exported multitables) and other options to customize the exported tables. Table cells can now contain estimates of standard deviation and standard error, and column summaries can include the median of numeric values as well as the standard deviation for the column and standard error of the mean. Pairwise column significance tests can be conducted at the standard 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New hypothesis testing features in Crunch</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-hypothesis-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-hypothesis-tests/</guid>
      <description>Crunch tab book exports now include a new hypothesis testing option that computes all possible comparisons between columns of a two-way table. When users select the &amp;ldquo;Column t-test&amp;rdquo; option in the “Export tab book… &amp;gt; Customize” panel, columns in output will be lettered and differences that are significant at the .05 significance level are indicated by letters underneath the cell with the higher percentage. See here for details.
An example of the exported result is shown below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Multitable Export</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-this-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/export-this-table/</guid>
      <description>Export all on a single page Multitables are a great way to quickly find key relationships in your data. When exporting multitables, you now have three choices, allowing you to create just the right export for your needs.
Export this table – instantly grab an XLSX file of just what you see on screen, using whatever display settings you have currently selected. Export this table (saved settings) – instantly grab an XLSX file of the table that you see on screen but with whatever settings you’ve chosen in the Export tab book &amp;gt; Customize panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tab Book Improvements</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/tab-book-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/tab-book-improvements/</guid>
      <description>We first released the tab book feature a while back, and since then, we’ve collected a number of great suggestions for how to enrich the feature. Tab books produce a static set of tables out of many variables and put results in an Excel sheet, for offline use when you don’t need interactive features like new filters or different weights. Our recent release includes several of those enhancements, most of which are new options available to you in the “export tab book” panel.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
