<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Careers on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Careers on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Business Development Manager / Inside Sales Representative</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:21:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada, Seattle preferred
What you&amp;rsquo;ll do
The Business Development Manager will have responsibility for driving market share, qualifying leads that build pipeline for the sales organization, and for closing smaller deals. The BDR will follow up on web inquiries, pre‐qualify leads, close smaller opportunities, and develop larger leads to the point of handoff to outside sales. In addition to inbound inquiries the BDR will perform prospecting, marketing event outreach and perform general sales development functions to build a pipeline within targeted accounts designated by management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Sales and Customer Success Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-sales-customer-success-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:21:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-sales-customer-success-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Customer Success
Work Location: Remote, United States, preferably EST or CST time zones
Are you a technically-oriented, quantitative market researcher looking for a change in direction? You should consider putting your technical skills to work in software, specifically, analytic software for market research.
Crunch.io is a rapidly growing, market-defining company in the analytics SaaS marketplace. We’re a company on the rise. We’ve built a revolutionary platform that transforms our customers’ ability to drive insight from market research and survey data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Lead, SRE and Devops</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/team-lead-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/team-lead-operations/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP Software Engineering
Work location: Forever 100% remote within Western Hemisphere timezones and work hours
Direct reports: 3-5
We are hiring a Team Lead over Systems Engineering and Operations to help expand our platform and operations excellence. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You will be self-motivated and disciplined in order to work with our fully distributed team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Manager</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/product-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:29:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/product-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Product Development
Work location: Remote, United States
Contract type: Permanent | Full-time
People manager: No
Crunch.io is seeking a Product Manager, to help us build the tools for the next generation of analytics tools for survey data. You will align with our workflows team, based in US Mountain Time, providing them with both big picture product vision and day-to-day delivery support. You will collaborate internally and externally to develop a vision for how users can work together to share and move data and insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Customer Support Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-customer-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 14:41:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-customer-support/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Manager of Customer Service
Work location: Remote
Do you work with market research data? Looking for a change of direction away from traditional market research data processing and analysis? Here is an opportunity to join the supplier side, in software.
We have a growing product and user base and need an organized, detail-oriented person to join our customer support team for our online data analysis and reporting app: Crunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Manager, Software Project Management</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/software-project-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/software-project-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP Software Engineering
Work location: North America, 100% remote
Direct reports: 8 to 12 software engineers
We are hiring an Engineering Manager to help expand our platform and operations excellence. The successful candidate will have been a software engineer and has grown into a project manager and team manager role, or possibly an experienced software project manager with no programming background. We invite you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators, helping make our platform faster, more secure, and reliable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Reliability/Devops Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/site-reliability-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/site-reliability-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Team Lead, SRE and Devops
Work location: Forever 100% remote within Western Hemisphere timezones and work hours
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring an experienced Site Reliability Engineer to help expand our platform and operations excellence. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You will be self-motivated and disciplined in order to work with our fully distributed team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization Specialist</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/data-visualization-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 11:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/data-visualization-specialist/</guid>
      <description>We are looking for a world-class Data Visualization Specialist to join our remote-first and globally distributed team at Crunch.io—the platform for collaborative data analysis. In this role, you will be working with a team of data scientists, industry experts, market research organizations, designers, and engineers; creating cutting-edge data visualizations for companies ranging from small-to-medium sized businesses to Fortune 500 organizations. This remote position reports to our VP of Product and will work closely with our Senior Director of Analytics and Product, Design, and Engineering teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Software Delivery Manager
Work location: Anywhere, 100% remote
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring a Python Developer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features and build the future for how we deploy our products faster and safer while increasing the availability and reliability of our systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced React Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/react-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:45:00 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/react-developer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Software Delivery Manager
Work location: Anywhere, 100% remote
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring an Advanced React Developer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features, explore different ways of problem solving, and discover, explain, and defend your choices in implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Executive, New Business</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada
The Account Executive will be responsible for driving sales of Crunch products within an assigned geographical region and market segment. The AE will represent Crunch and manage all aspects of the sales process including: lead management, qualification, evaluation, close and account care and will play an integral role in the success of the overall sales team. This is a quota‐carrying sales position.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
