<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Careers on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Careers on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Crunch.io is an innovative analytics company in the market research industry. We offer a survey data analysis platform that allows market researchers, analysts, and marketers to collaborate in a secure, cloud-based environment, using an intuitive drag-and-drop interface. Crunch users can quickly gain insights from their data and communicate them to their clients.
We are hiring a Python Engineer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior R Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/senior-r-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/senior-r-developer/</guid>
      <description>Reporting to: VP of Product  Location: Anywhere
Crunch.io is seeking a talented, motivated, and versatile human to help lead the development of our R data science products. Crunch provides a modern platform for survey data analysis, and a central feature of our product is the ability to manipulate and analyze datasets stored in the cloud using R. As senior R developer, you will have three main responsibilities. First, you will work with the rest of our team to design and implement novel features that deliver real value and change our clients’ workflows for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate JavaScript Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/javascript-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 16:45:00 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/javascript-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is seeking talented, motivated engineers to join our fully remote team building interactive data applications. As a part of growing front-end team, you will work with five experienced JavaScript developers and two designers constantly improving our users’ experience. You will also collaborate with others throughout our organization and technology stack to build products that are revolutionizing the way our clients achieve their business goals.
On the front-end team, we feel strongly about developing solutions that are both technically and aesthetically sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Development Manager</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:39:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reporting to: VP of Sales Location: Remote, United States or Canada, (Seattle preferred)
Crunch.io is a market-defining company in the analytics SaaS marketplace. We’re a company on the rise. We’ve built a revolutionary platform that transforms our customers’ ability to drive insight from market research and survey data.
Crunch offers a complete survey data analysis platform that allows market researchers, analysts, and marketers to collaborate in a secure, cloud-based environment, using a simple, intuitive drag-and-drop interface to prepare, analyze, visualize and deliver survey data and analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Executive, New Business</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</guid>
      <description>Reporting to: VP of Sales Location: United States
Crunch.io is a market-defining company in the analytics SaaS marketplace. We’re a company on the rise. We offer revolutionary products that transform our customers’ ability to drive insight from market research and survey data. Crunch offers a complete survey data analysis platform that allows market researchers, analysts, and marketers to collaborate in a secure, cloud-based environment, using a simple, intuitive drag-and-drop interface to prepare, analyze, visualize and deliver survey data and analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Programs Manager</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/marketing-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:54:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/marketing-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reporting to: VP of Marketing Location: Remote, United States or Canada, (Seattle preferred)
Crunch.io is a market-defining company in the analytics SaaS marketplace. We’re a company on the rise. We’ve built a revolutionary platform that transforms our customers’ ability to drive insight from market research and survey data.
Crunch offers a complete survey data analysis platform that allows market researchers, analysts, and marketers to collaborate in a secure, cloud-based environment, using a simple, intuitive drag-and-drop interface to prepare, analyze, visualize and deliver survey data and analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>