<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Careers on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Careers on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Site Reliability Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/site-reliability-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/site-reliability-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Team Lead, Systems Engineering and Operations
Work location: USA or Canada, 100% remote
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring an experienced Site Reliability Engineer to help expand our platform and operations excellence. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You will be self-motivated and disciplined in order to work with our fully distributed team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization Specialist</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/data-visualization-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 11:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/data-visualization-specialist/</guid>
      <description>We are looking for a world-class Data Visualization Specialist to join our remote-first and globally distributed team at Crunch.io—the platform for collaborative data analysis. In this role, you will be working with a team of data scientists, industry experts, market research organizations, designers, and engineers; creating cutting-edge data visualizations for companies ranging from small-to-medium sized businesses to Fortune 500 organizations. This remote position reports to our VP of Product and will work closely with our Senior Director of Analytics and Product, Design, and Engineering teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Software Delivery Manager
Work location: Anywhere, 100% remote
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring a Python Developer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features and build the future for how we deploy our products faster and safer while increasing the availability and reliability of our systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced React Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/react-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 16:45:00 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/react-developer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: Software Delivery Manager
Work location: Anywhere, 100% remote
Direct reports: 0
We are hiring an Advanced React Developer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features, explore different ways of problem solving, and discover, explain, and defend your choices in implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Director, Professional Services</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/director-professional-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 15:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/director-professional-services/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: President, Crunch.io
Location: Remote or at one of our offices
The Senior Director, Professional Services will be responsible for understanding customer needs and processes and adapting them to Crunch workflows via a combination of training, consulting, and customized software development. We are a startup so digging in and solving problems across a variety of areas is part of the fun of the job.
Our start-up culture is casual and high-energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Sales and Customer Success Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-sales-customer-success-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-sales-customer-success-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Location: Remote, United States
The Technical Sales Engineer (TSE) is responsible for explaining and demonstrating to prospective customers how Crunch works and then making sure it works once they are customers. We are a startup so digging in and solving problems across a variety of areas is part of the fun of the job.
Our start-up culture is casual and high-energy. We all work remote, with the center of gravity in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Development Representative</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-representative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:39:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-representative/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada, (Seattle preferred)
The Business Development Representative has responsibility for driving market share, qualifying leads that build pipeline for the sales organization, and for closing smaller deals. The BDR will follow up on web inquiries, pre‐qualify leads, close smaller opportunities, and develop larger leads to the point of hand-off to outside sales. In addition to inbound inquiries the BDR will perform prospecting, marketing event outreach and perform general sales development functions to build a pipeline within targeted accounts designated by management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Executive, New Business</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada
The Account Executive will be responsible for driving sales of Crunch products within an assigned geographical region and market segment. The AE will represent Crunch and manage all aspects of the sales process including: lead management, qualification, evaluation, close and account care and will play an integral role in the success of the overall sales team. This is a quota‐carrying sales position.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
