<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Join our team! on Crunch</title>
    <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Join our team! on Crunch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://crunch.io/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Backend Engineer</title>
      <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/senior-backend-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crunch.io/jobs/senior-backend-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is looking for experienced Python developers who want to be part of a team building a large-scale cloud-based analytics platform. Based on your talents, you will find yourself a member of one of our small teams helping move our platform forward. This means adding value to our product by reducing friction in our client&amp;rsquo;s workflows, providing new and interesting ways to manipulate their data, and allow them to publish their results with the expectation of massive scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Database Engineer</title>
      <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/database-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crunch.io/jobs/database-engineer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full-Stack Engineer</title>
      <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/full-stack-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crunch.io/jobs/full-stack-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is seeking talented, motivated, and versatile software developers to help build our next-generation dataset-management platform, all the way from physical bits to complete analyses and visualizations. You would work with the rest of our team to design and implement novel features that deliver real value and change our clients’ workflows for the better. We’re looking for people who like to write beautiful, interactive, scalable software that just happens to run in a web browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript Engineer</title>
      <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/javascript-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crunch.io/jobs/javascript-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is seeking talented, motivated front-end engineers to build our interactive data applications. You would work with the rest of our team to help build a product that is changing the way our clients do their work. Both technical and aesthetic details matter greatly to you. (You like to use both arrow functions and en-dashes appropriately.) You want to surround yourself with talented peers who share your dedication. In short, you write solid, thoroughly tested, and readable code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Delivery and Support Developer</title>
      <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/support-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crunch.io/jobs/support-developer/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is seeking a highly motivated person to join our development team in a delivery and support role. We have a growing product and user base, and we need an organized, detail-oriented person to help us better serve our users. We must ensure that all support requests are handled in a timely, professional manner, and that we provide enough rich online documentation and examples that our users can answer many questions themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Manager</title>
      <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/product-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crunch.io/jobs/product-manager/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is seeking an experienced product manager to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI/UX Developer</title>
      <link>http://crunch.io/jobs/ux-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://crunch.io/jobs/ux-developer/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is looking for a skilled frontend developer/designer that takes pride in having extreme attention to detail and understands how to marry aesthetics and usability. You should be passionate about creating great user experiences and always advocate for them. We are looking for people who lives in the intersection of design and coding. You enjoy turning conceptual ideas into sketches or wireframes using a visual editor but also love to bring those designs to the web using HTML, CSS, and some JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>