<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Careers on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Careers on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:08:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Director, Professional Services</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/director-professional-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 15:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/director-professional-services/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: President, Crunch.io
Location: Remote or at one of our offices
The Senior Director, Professional Services will be responsible for understanding customer needs and processes and adapting them to Crunch workflows via a combination of training, consulting, and customized software development. We are a startup so digging in and solving problems across a variety of areas is part of the fun of the job.
Our start-up culture is casual and high-energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Sales and Customer Success Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-sales-customer-success-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-sales-customer-success-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Location: Remote, United States
The Technical Sales Engineer (TSE) is responsible for explaining and demonstrating to prospective customers how Crunch works and then making sure it works once they are customers. We are a startup so digging in and solving problems across a variety of areas is part of the fun of the job.
Our start-up culture is casual and high-energy. We all work remote, with the center of gravity in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python API Developer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-api-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/python-api-developer/</guid>
      <description>We are hiring a Python API Developer to help develop our platform. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You would help us deliver new features and build the future for how we deploy our products faster and safer while increasing the availability and reliability of our systems. You will explore different ways of problem solving and discover, explain, and defend your choices in implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Delivery Manager</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/software-delivery-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/software-delivery-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP Software Engineering
Work location: Anywhere
Direct reports: 6-10
We are hiring a Software Delivery Manager to help expand our platform and operations excellence, someone who has been a software engineer and has graduated into a delivery manager role. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You will be self-motivated and disciplined in order to work with our fully distributed team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineer in Test (SDET)</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/sdet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 14:09:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/sdet/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP Software Engineering
Work location: Anywhere
Employment type: Contract to Permanent
We are hiring a QA Engineer to help us in three key areas.
 We need someone with cypress.io experience to migrate a few hundred nightwatch.js end-to-end browser/selenium tests to Cypress.io. We need help writing JavaScript unit tests for our Angular/React front-end to improve our test code coverage to 100%. We need someone who can work directly with our product managers to design, refine, and implement a better end-to-end testing strategy that covers all of our important user flow and use cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Lead, Systems Engineering and Operations</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/team-lead-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/team-lead-operations/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP Software Engineering
Work location: Anywhere
Direct reports: 2
We are hiring a Team Lead over Systems Engineering and Operations to help expand our platform and operations excellence. We are inviting you to join our small, fully remote team of developers and operators helping make our platform faster, more secure, and more reliable. You will be self-motivated and disciplined in order to work with our fully distributed team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Writer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 00:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/technical-writer/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP Software Engineering
Work location: Anywhere
Employment type: Contract to Permanent
Crunch.io is seeking a curious, meticulous, friendly technical writer work with the rest of our team on a contract basis. Our platform has the potential to transform customers’ archaic workflows — if only they knew how. We need your help to convey and explain the powerful tools we are building to a variety of audiences, from highly technical implementation teams to end users learning about new features in a web application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate JavaScript Engineer</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/javascript-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 16:45:00 +0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/javascript-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Work location: Anywhere
Crunch is seeking talented, motivated engineers to join our fully remote team building interactive data applications. As a part of growing front-end team, you will work with five experienced JavaScript developers and two designers constantly improving our users’ experience. You will also collaborate with others throughout our organization and technology stack to build products that are revolutionizing the way our clients achieve their business goals.
On the front-end team, we feel strongly about developing solutions that are both technically and aesthetically sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Development Manager</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:39:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/business-development-manager/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada, (Seattle preferred)
The Business Development Manager has responsibility for driving market share, qualifying leads that build pipeline for the sales organization, and for closing smaller deals. The BDR will follow up on web inquiries, pre‐qualify leads, close smaller opportunities, and develop larger leads to the point of hand-off to outside sales. In addition to inbound inquiries the BDR will perform prospecting, marketing event outreach and perform general sales development functions to build a pipeline within targeted accounts designated by management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Executive, New Business</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:08:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/jobs/account-executive/</guid>
      <description>Reports to: VP of Sales
Work location: Remote, United States or Canada
The Account Executive will be responsible for driving sales of Crunch products within an assigned geographical region and market segment. The AE will represent Crunch and manage all aspects of the sales process including: lead management, qualification, evaluation, close and account care and will play an integral role in the success of the overall sales team. This is a quota‐carrying sales position.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>