<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>differences on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/differences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in differences on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 12:17:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/differences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Subtotals and calculated differences can now be shown on graphs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/graphing-subtotals-and-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 12:17:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/graphing-subtotals-and-differences/</guid>
      <description>Subtotals have been a feature of Crunch for years, and calculated differences were added to the feature set in May 2021. They&amp;rsquo;ve been popular features in tables and thanks to this latest release, they&amp;rsquo;re now available in graphs too. Both subtotals and differences can now be displayed in graphs in Tables &amp;amp; Graphs mode, as well as on dashboards and in PPTX exports, giving you the flexibility to display, save and report these summary statistics just like any other variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add subtotals to multiple response variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals-mr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 12:30:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotals-mr/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors have been able to add subtotals (a.k.a. “nets”) to categorical and categorical array variables for a long time, but this hasn’t been the case for multiple response variables. There are many applications for subtotals on multiple response variables — a common one is a group of products or sub-brands within a brand, or a grouping of statements into themes. Previously, users had to define new variables with often complex logic to describe each combination, and then hide the input variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show calculated differences between categories</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotal-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 13:27:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/subtotal-differences/</guid>
      <description>You’ve been able to create subtotals in Crunch for a long time, and they’re great for quickly seeing what proportion of respondents hold similar views, such as any level of agreement with a statement or any level of liking of a brand etc. But sometimes you also need to take into account the strength of opposing views — those who disagree or those who dislike, and for that you want to sum those who agree and take away the sum of those who disagree, leaving you with an overall measure you can use for simple comparisons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
