<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>graphs on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/graphs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in graphs on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:11:57 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/graphs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfect your PowerPoint decks with many new edit controls</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:11:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/slides-editable-from-deck/</guid>
      <description>When you create an analysis, you may need to edit it further for a PowerPoint export: for example, perhaps you want to hide &amp;lsquo;Not sure&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Prefer not to answer&amp;rsquo; categories, rename long labels, re-order the categories, give the whole analysis a descriptive title, or even simply change the coloring. You can now make these adjustments and more, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find all of those changes reflected in your PowerPoint and Excel exports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show value labels on graphs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/show-value-labels/</guid>
      <description>Users can now decide whether to show value labels for graphs and charts, both in Tables &amp;amp; Graphs mode and on dashboards. Value labels are these small numbers on graphs that show you the value represented by that bar/column/segment&amp;hellip;
 With the new feature turned on, these value labels will be displayed on all graphs you create. With the feature turned off (the default), the user needs to hover over a chart element to see a tool-tip with this value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Deck Exports</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 10:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/pptx-exports/</guid>
      <description>We know that for many, PowerPoint slides remain central to delivering results and to paraphrase Mark Twain, &amp;ldquo;reports of PowerPoint&amp;rsquo;s death have been greatly exagerated&amp;rdquo;. Crunch has long offered exports of analyses and tab books to Excel files, which, in addition to their own value, enabled people to get results from Crunch to PowerPoint by copying a cell range from Excel into a slide. That’s a bit tedious, though, and we wanted to do better, which is why we are excited to announce that PowerPoint exports from Crunch are now available if you have ‘Early access’ enabled in the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is designed to make data accessible to many different audiences that have varying needs, expectations, and technical abilities. Our browse and analyze views allow data owners and analysts to quickly explore and analyze interesting insights in potentially large, complex datasets. However, not everyone has time to explore a dataset&amp;mdash;some need to see key findings at a glance.
To meet this executive-type need, we&amp;rsquo;re introducing a new dashboard feature.
 This dashboard provides a quick view of up to four analyses, right when you open a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>:bar_chart: New Header, New Font, New Graphs :chart_with_upwards_trend: </title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/visual-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 11:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/visual-updates/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been working on updating and improving the look of Crunch, and we wanted to take moment to call out a few of the recent improvements.
Let’s start at the top You may have noticed that we recently updated the Crunch header.
 This new top bar provides a more unified look throughout the application, and allows us to move user settings, dataset settings, and project settings into unobtrusive and consistently located dropdown menus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>