<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>time series on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/time-series/</link>
    <description>Recent content in time series on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 13:39:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/time-series/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crunch&#39;s new visualizations for time-series analyses and trackers are now extended to Date/Time variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/date-time-variables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 13:39:46 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/date-time-variables/</guid>
      <description>Back in April this year, we announced that a great new visualization was available for time series analyses that used the new &amp;ldquo;Categorical Date&amp;rdquo; variable type. Existing time plots that used the older Date/Time variable type were unaffected and continued to use the previous line graph component. Since then, we&amp;rsquo;ve worked to extend the new line graph functionality to those original Date/Time variables so that everyone can benefit from their better design and functionality, and we can now announce that all time plots will be using the new visualization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great new visualizations for time-series analyses and trackers</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-time-plots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 08:20:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/new-time-plots/</guid>
      <description>Line graphs are great at showing how values are changing over time and therefore ideal for tracking studies. Crunch&amp;rsquo;s line graphs have been completely redesigned to offer some great new features as well as improved usability and flexibility.&#xA;Category selection&#xA;Line graphs become really hard to read when there are lots of lines shown simultaneously, so Crunch now defaults to showing just the top 5, but you can pick whichever combination of lines (including showing more or fewer than 5) from the new &amp;ldquo;Select categories&amp;rdquo; interface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perform trend analysis on wave data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:18:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/trend-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In time series analysis, we want to be able to identify trends. As we collect data, random fluctuations can obfuscate a trend. Smoothing is an analytic process whereby we ‘iron out’ differences between time periods by taking the average of previous periods. This is also known as a moving average. You can now apply smoothing to your analyses with just a few clicks. In the smoothing tab accessed by clicking ⋮ select ‘One-sided moving average’ and choose the number of periods to ‘look back’ at each point.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
