<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation on Crunch</title>
    <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Automation on Crunch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 09:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our new open-source tool eliminates the &#34;works on my machine&#34; problem for automated end-to-end browser testing. Ensure that everyone&#39;s &#34;machine&#34; has the same configuration using Docker.</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/nightwatch-selenium-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/nightwatch-selenium-docker/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch we greatly value tests. We have unit tests, functional tests, and the stack wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be complete without end-to-end tests. Good tests allow us to update code quickly and confidently.
For our end-to-end testing we use Nightwatch.js, a JavaScript testing tool that uses Selenium to drive a browser to perform tests. Our goal is to be able to test our Python backend, our REST APIs, and the behavior of our JavaScript single-page application, using a real browser, running real code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Travis-CI to Build Static Sites</title>
      <link>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/building-the-blog-on-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 21:12:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/blog/building-the-blog-on-travis/</guid>
      <description>At Crunch.io, we&amp;rsquo;re fervent believers in automation. If something requires a human to remember to do an extra manual step, it won&amp;rsquo;t happen consistently. We automate test running so that we don&amp;rsquo;t have to fix the same bug twice. We write code to do tedious tasks so that we can devote our mental energy to harder problems. We automate processes and policies so that developers don&amp;rsquo;t have remember the right things to do—the build and continuous-integration systems guide us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>