<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>datasets on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/datasets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in datasets on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 17:39:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/datasets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Give a great welcome to your customers by branding and customizing the appearance of folders</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/folder-homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 17:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/folder-homepage/</guid>
      <description>Crunch’s folders give you the power to organize your datasets and control access. Now folders can also be a great landing page for new and existing data consumers.
Crunch’s folders give you the power to organize your datasets and control access. Now folders can also be a great landing page for new and existing data consumers.
 Examples of usage Expected use cases for these homepages include&amp;hellip;
 A welcome message for analysts accessing your data An opportunity to add your branding and logos Privacy notices and other terms &amp;amp; conditions, including external links Guidance on how to navigate folders and sub-folders, including shortcutss to particular resources Promotional text, images and/or videos for other products and services that you offer (an opportunity for cross-selling) including links to further information Hints and tips for using Crunch - &amp;ldquo;Did you know&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplified options for Dataset Sharing</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-sharing/</guid>
      <description>The sharing options for a dataset have been simplified and consolidated. Previously, both Share and Members links were visible to Dataset Editors. To simplify, Dataset Editors can only now see the Members link. The Share link option for Dataset Editors has been removed.
For Dataset Viewers, the sharing option with Share link has not changed.
Below we have outlined how you can share a dataset for different permission levels: Editors and Viewers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Organization of Datasets</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</guid>
      <description>Dataset folders allow you to organize your data hierarchically, similar to a file system as you might see in Windows Explorer or MacOS Finder. Folders make finding, organizing, and sharing data more intuitive.
  Folders can be used to organize large collections of datasets into more manageable units. If your organization imports data from many sources or has a large archive of previously imported data, you can organize them by source, time of import/survey, subject, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
