<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>datasets on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/datasets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in datasets on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:29:38 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/datasets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Easily create and share subsets of your datasets with different user groups</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:29:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-views/</guid>
      <description>Dataset Views: Quickly Create, Deliver, and Share Data Subsets
 It’s increasingly common to collect data for multiple clients or multiple groups of stakeholders in one single survey. Whether for an Omnibus product, a syndicated data product or simply different regional groupings, it can be challenging to meet the different data needs of these client and stakeholder groups with a single dataset. To meet this need, Crunch has developed Dataset Views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give a great welcome to your customers by branding and customizing the appearance of folders</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/folder-homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 15:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/folder-homepage/</guid>
      <description>Crunch’s folders give you the power to organize your datasets and control access. Now folders can also be a great landing page for new and existing data consumers.
Folder Homepages can contain images, formatted text, embedded videos and links to other resources to provide Crunch customization, as well as to aide in navigation to other resources such as terms and conditions. You can tailor the experience for your teammates and clients when they arrive into Crunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplified options for Dataset Sharing</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-sharing/</guid>
      <description>The sharing options for a dataset have been simplified and consolidated. Previously, both Share and Members links were visible to Dataset Editors. To simplify, Dataset Editors can only now see the Members link. The Share link option for Dataset Editors has been removed.
For Dataset Viewers, the sharing option with Share link has not changed.
Below we have outlined how you can share a dataset for different permission levels: Editors and Viewers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Organization of Datasets</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-folders/</guid>
      <description>Dataset folders allow you to organize your data hierarchically, similar to a file system as you might see in Windows Explorer or MacOS Finder. Folders make finding, organizing, and sharing data more intuitive.
  Folders can be used to organize large collections of datasets into more manageable units. If your organization imports data from many sources or has a large archive of previously imported data, you can organize them by source, time of import/survey, subject, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
