<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dashboards on Online survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/dashboards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dashboards on Online survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 11:27:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/dashboards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sort your graph categories automatically</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sort-by-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 11:27:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/sort-by-value/</guid>
      <description>You’ve been able to sort categories in tables in Crunch for a long time, but previously when you switched to a graph, that sorting was lost and the graph would show the categories in their original variable order. Now, the sorting you apply in a table will be carried through into a graph when you switch visualization type, as well as being made part of the analysis definition when you save a graph to the deck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crunch Automation: A blueprint for building a solid home for your data</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/blog/automation/crunch-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 11:44:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/blog/automation/crunch-automation/</guid>
      <description>Crunch Automation serves as a declarative history of transformations that have been done to a dataset. This is important to understand, because it informs you how you go about writing, running, editing and replicating datasets.
With SPSS syntax, it
directly manipulates an SPSS datafile (eg: .sav file) is not designed with survey analysis in mind doesn’t set up derivations like Crunch does (it hard-codes anything you do as a new variable) doesn’t stay with the datafile (you keep your syntax separate from the datafile), and, importantly, alters your variables by overwriting the already-hard-coded variables with more syntax (which you can do endlessly) Crunch Automation is the opposite in these respects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export dashboards or the tabs you want, with the new selective tab exports feature</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 09:39:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/selective-tab-exports/</guid>
      <description>Exporting from dashboards just got more flexible. Instead of always having to export the whole dashboard, users are now able to choose between exporting the whole dashboard (still the default), exporting the currently viewed tab, or choosing a custom selection of one or more tabs to export.
The new, simplified “Export…” option opens the new Export panel which gives the choice of PowerPoint or Excel formats, but for dashboards with tabs, it also now contains a “Tabs” control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combine categories in dashboard filter variables</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/multiple-selections-in-groups/</guid>
      <description>The Groups on dashboards can now optionally allow multiple category selections to effectively combine categories in the filter. Dashboard editors can set an option on the configuration screen for dashboard “Groups” that allows users to make multiple selections within each variable. For example, if you choose an age categories variable as a group and turn on this new option, the dashboard users will be able to select both “18–24” and “25–34” simultaneously, thereby creating a filter that includes anyone aged 18–34.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize your tables for export or dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 09:26:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/editable-tables/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve already been able to customize saved graphs, but now you can make those same edits to the rows and columns of saved tables, either for export or for display in dashboards. More specifically, you can now&amp;hellip;
Hide any rows and/or columns of a table, including calculated rows/columns such as subtotals, leaving only those you want your export/dashboard consumers to see. Simply uncheck the box next to the row/column to hide it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use custom color palettes for your saved analyses</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 12:14:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/color-palettes/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been possible for some time to set custom colors for saved analyses in Crunch, but it&amp;rsquo;s been necessary to do this on a one-by-one basis which can be laborious and open to inconsistency. We now offer the ability to create custom color palettes, defined at the organization level, at folder levels, or both, which apply your chosen colors to newly created analyses as well as offering alternatives (e.g. for scales) that can be applied easily, as needed for particular analyses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding KPI tiles to dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-kpi-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:03:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-kpi-tile/</guid>
      <description>Dashboards can now contain KPI analyses that take a single value from a table and present it in a tile. Great for when there&amp;rsquo;s a key metric you want to highlight or track.
Dataset editors can now add KPI analyses like these to dashboards. This allows you to show a key company metric – e.g. Brand Awareness – as a prominent value that grabs attention.
To create one, simply save an analysis of any kind – table, chart or variable card – that contains the value you want to show as a KPI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard tabs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</guid>
      <description>Dashboard tiles can now be placed across multiple tabs, making it easier to navigate large dashboards. As an editor, you are now able to:
Create new tabs (as many as you&amp;rsquo;d like)
Move tiles from one tab to another
Give tabs meaningful names to aid navigation
Delete tabs, choosing whether to delete any tiles or move them to another tab
See our support documentation to get started.
We&amp;rsquo;d love your feedback at support@crunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding rich-text tiles to dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 13:07:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can now add rich-text tiles to a dashboard. This can be used for dashboard analysis, terms and conditions, privacy notices, fieldwork dates and anything else the editor may wish to display. As an editor you are now able to:
Compose text content to display as tiles using a WYSIWYG editor - no coding skills required.
See a real-time preview of how your tile is going to look as you type and make formatting changes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filtering dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 10:16:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can add one or more variables to be used as filters across an entire dashboard with a simple drag-and-drop interface. This allows all dashboard viewers to get more out of your dashboards by customizing their view of the data. For example:
Add demographic variables such as gender, age, education level, region, and ethnicity to allow your viewers to drill down on the customer populations that interest them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customizable dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 09:56:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</guid>
      <description>What are Crunch dashboards? A dashboard is a special view of your data that has been prepared with pre-made analyses — tables and graphs — designed to highlight key points for instant insight. Dashboards are great for conveying key information, drawn from your data, for users who don’t have the time (or the inclination) to do their own analysis. Crunch dashboards allow you to combine your important findings into a single display, perfect for sharing with colleagues and other end users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is designed to make data accessible to many different audiences that have varying needs, expectations, and technical abilities. Our browse and analyze views allow data owners and analysts to quickly explore and analyze interesting insights in potentially large, complex datasets. However, not everyone has time to explore a dataset&amp;mdash;some need to see key findings at a glance.
To meet this executive-type need, we&amp;rsquo;re introducing a new dashboard feature.
This dashboard provides a quick view of up to four analyses, right when you open a dataset.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
