<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dashboards on Modern survey data analysis</title>
    <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/dashboards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dashboards on Modern survey data analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:19:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/tags/dashboards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard tabs</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-tabs/</guid>
      <description>Dashboard tiles can now be placed across multiple tabs, making it easier to navigate large dashboards. As an editor, you are now able to:
  Create new tabs (as many as you&#39;d like)
  Move tiles from one tab to another
  Give tabs meaningful names to aid navigation
  Delete tabs, choosing whether to delete any tiles or move them to another tab
  See our support documentation to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding rich-text tiles to dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 13:07:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-text-tile/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can now add rich-text tiles to a dashboard. This can be used for dashboard analysis, terms and conditions, privacy notices, fieldwork dates and anything else the editor may wish to display. As an editor you are now able to:
  Compose text content to display as tiles using a WYSIWYG editor - no coding skills required.
  See a real-time preview of how your tile is going to look as you type and make formatting changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filtering dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 10:16:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboard-filtering/</guid>
      <description>Dataset editors can add one or more variables to be used as filters across an entire dashboard with a simple drag-and-drop interface. This allows all dashboard viewers to get more out of your dashboards by customizing their view of the data. For example:
  Add demographic variables such as gender, age, education level, region, and ethnicity to allow your viewers to drill down on the customer populations that interest them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizable dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 09:56:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dashboards/</guid>
      <description>What are Crunch dashboards? A dashboard is a special view of your data that has been prepared with pre-made analyses — tables and graphs — designed to highlight key points for instant insight. Dashboards are great for conveying key information, drawn from your data, for users who don’t have the time (or the inclination) to do their own analysis. Crunch dashboards allow you to combine your important findings into a single display, perfect for sharing with colleagues and other end users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Dashboards</title>
      <link>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 23:20:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//crunch-io.github.io/crunchy/newsite/dev/features/dataset-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Crunch is designed to make data accessible to many different audiences that have varying needs, expectations, and technical abilities. Our browse and analyze views allow data owners and analysts to quickly explore and analyze interesting insights in potentially large, complex datasets. However, not everyone has time to explore a dataset&amp;mdash;some need to see key findings at a glance.
To meet this executive-type need, we&#39;re introducing a new dashboard feature.
 This dashboard provides a quick view of up to four analyses, right when you open a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>